Bonus Short Stories

The School Uniform That Doesn’t Fit

It was spring break in Japan, just as cherry blossoms were starting to bloom and before Amakawa Haruto was to start his third year of high school.

Meanwhile, Sumeragi Satsuki was beginning her first year of university and had started living alone to prepare herself to integrate into society. She was currently organizing her belongings in the apartment she had moved into. She opened one of her many suitcases of clothes and took out an outfit to look at.

“Whoa, this brings back memories...” Satsuki blinked. “Wait, why is my middle school uniform here?”

She snapped back to her senses. Right—the school uniform of the middle school she attended three years ago was packed in her suitcase. The shirt had a white base with a red scarf at the chest, and the dress was a pleated ocher. It was a generic sailor uniform design.

I wonder if it still fits...? Satsuki hummed in contemplation. I’m sure I’ll fit... Right?

Her height and weight shouldn’t have changed that much since middle school, but three years had passed since she graduated. The possibility that she couldn’t fit in it anymore flashed through her head, making her expression fall with uncertainty. However, her curiosity made her face her fear.

Well, I guess it wouldn’t hurt to try...

Despite her hesitation, Satsuki decided to try on her middle school uniform. She removed her clothes and pushed her arms through the sleeves of the uniform she last wore three years ago. The shirt was a little tight on her, but—

“See, it fits!” Satsuki exhaled in relief.

But it hadn’t been easy. Her bust had grown bigger, so her shirt was shorter, almost revealing her belly. She’d also put on more weight around her hips, making her skirt feel shorter. It wasn’t as though anyone could see her, but Satsuki blushed in embarrassment anyway.

“Whoa...”

She walked to the bathroom and checked her appearance in the mirror. It really didn’t fit her, and it made her feel like she was cosplaying.

Let’s take this off now.

Just as Satsuki thought that—Knock knock: the sound of someone knocking on her front door.

“A knock... Oh, c-could that be Haruto?”

The apartment Satsuki had moved into was in the same building as the apartment Haruto rented. Haruto had offered to help out after she moved in, but there was the possibility that the electricity contract hadn’t been completed yet, so they agreed he would knock when visiting.

“W-Wait, it’s Haruto, right? Hold on a minute!” Satsuki yelled towards the door.

“All right.”

It really was Haruto outside the door. Once Satsuki confirmed that, she set about taking off her sailor uniform in a hurry. However—

“H-Huh?”

She tried to pull her arm back out of the sleeve, but the fabric was tough and got caught midway. She put in more strength to remove it in a fluster.

“Ugh...”

She had forcefully twisted her body too far, crushing her chest in pain.

I’ll start from the head, then...

Satsuki gave up on the sleeves and pulled the fabric on her chest upwards. But once the cloth was pulled up to her eyes, it wouldn’t budge.

I-It really is too tight...! Wh-What should I do? I can’t keep Haruto waiting forever...!

With her entire belly revealed, Satsuki panicked. However, a short while later, she marched towards the entrance as though she had made up her mind. She was still wearing her school uniform.

“Listen, Haruto. You’re about to witness a woman’s secret. You’re a gentleman, so I’m sure you know already, but you must keep quiet about this from everyone. Got it?” Satsuki suddenly demanded through the door.

“Huh?”

“Got it?! I’m going to open the door!”

“Y-Yes ma’am...!”

Haruto had no idea what was happening, but nodded under the pressure Satsuki was exerting. Seconds later, she opened the door...

Haruto was immediately greeted by the sight of Satsuki in a sailor uniform that didn’t fit her. Huh? Why a sailor uniform? was the question written on his face, but he didn’t say anything out loud. Instead, he simply stared at her in a daze.

“N-No staring! I’ll explain inside, so just come in!”

Satsuki tugged on the hem of her shirt in an attempt to hide her belly, then grabbed Haruto’s arm with a furious blush and quickly dragged him inside.

Daily Life for the First Time in a While

The morning after Rio brought Christina and Flora back to Rodania, he returned to Celia and Aishia in his Rodanian mansion and would stay there until they returned to Galarc.

After he finished his morning sword practice, Rio prepared breakfast for the three of them.

“Good morning, Celia.” He sensed Celia’s presence and greeted her without turning around.

“Morning, Rio...”

“Still sleepy?” Rio chuckled at Celia’s dazed reply. It wasn’t a particularly late time of day to get up—if anything, Rio was just an early bird.

“It’s just refreshing to see you here when I get up in the morning,” Celia said happily. They had been living separately lately, after all. Just then, Aishia materialized.

“Morning... I’m hungry. I want to eat Haruto’s cooking,” She said with a cute yawn. There were no live-in servants at this mansion, so Aishia was free to materialize while indoors. (When Rio was absent, they hired help from the consulate when necessary.)

“Morning. It’ll be ready soon—I just have to heat up some of the dishes, so wait just a minute.”

Seeing the two of them made Rio feel like he had really come home. It made him feel so happy that the corners of his mouth naturally turned upwards.

“I’ll bring over the dishes that are done.”

“I’ll help too. It smells great,” Aishia and Celia both said, taking the initiative.

“I haven’t made anything that complex.”

Today’s menu included bread, soup, salad, scrambled eggs, and sausages. A simple breakfast.

“Whatever you make is delicious. I’m looking forward to it. Oh, but Aishia and I improved our skills while you were gone too, you know? We’ll make lunch later, so please give it a try then! Isn’t that right, Aishia?” Celia offered.

“Yup.”

“I’m really looking forward to that.”

Rio basked in his peaceful daily life with the two of them.

Latifa’s Monopoly

In the forest on the outskirts of Rodania...

While Celia was at the consulate, Rio was visiting the stone house alone. He entered the barrier surrounding the area and instead of knocking, sent a few regular waves of magic essence towards the house. As soon as he confirmed he wasn’t an intruder, Latifa burst out.

“Welcome home, Onii-chan!” She hugged him enthusiastically. Miharu, Sara, Orphia, and Alma exited the house after her.

“I’m back.”

“Yup! What are you here for today? Where are Celia and Aishia?” Latifa looked up at him and asked, still clinging onto him.

“Celia has lectures in Rodania until evening. Aishia is protecting her. I wanted to see you, so I dropped by,” Rio replied while petting Latifa’s head.

“Really?! I’m so happy!”

“Shall we go inside first?”

“Okay!”

And so, Rio and the girls entered the house. Latifa was clinging to Rio’s arm.

“You just saw him the other day, but you’re sticking to him so closely again today, Latifa,” Sara said with a slight pout on her lips.

“Of course. I want to be with him every day of the year. That’s why I’m going to be by his side a lot today! Come on, let’s sit down.” Latifa huffed proudly and pulled Rio’s arm towards the sofa in the living room so they could sit down together.

“We’ll be leaving for the Galarc Kingdom in a few days, but I’ll try to visit as much as possible until then.”

“Okay!” Latifa strengthened her hold on Rio with a squeeze.

“If you’re staying until evening, that means we can eat lunch together today. Is there anything you’d like to eat?” Orphia asked happily.

“I’m fine with whatever you originally had planned.”

“We hadn’t decided what to make yet, so anything goes. Isn’t that right, Miharu?”

“Yup,” Miharu nodded.

“In that case, let’s eat something we can all make together! Like a barbeque!”

“That wouldn’t take much time, so it’s a great idea,” Rio said, on board with Latifa’s suggestion.

“Then it’s decided!”

Thus, it was decided that lunch would be a barbeque. That being said, it was still too early to eat, so their conversation continued for a while.

Normally, Aishia and Latifa would cling to Rio and Celia would try to stop Aishia right away, which Sara would jump on board with immediately, but neither Aishia nor Celia were here today.

“He he he...”

Latifa remained close to Rio while he was visiting. Sara had pointed out how she was being a bit too attached midway, but she appeared to be more reserved than usual without Celia around.

Rio and Latifa were currently seated on a three-seater sofa, but Latifa was completely monopolizing it. Because of that, she was in quite the good mood.

“Aren’t you jealous, Sara?” Alma suddenly asked.

“Yes, I... Wait, about what?!” Sara nodded reflexively, then panicked with a gasp.

“I’m talking about their sibling relationship, of course,” Alma said with a giggle.

“Right...” Sara nodded shyly, a faint blush on her face.

Chapter 1: Report

There were so many things to cover in Christina’s explanation that simply retelling the whole sequence of events took over ten minutes.

“And that’s all from me,” Christina said, wrapping up her summary of everything that took place.

“Hmm... It is a joyous occasion that you both have returned to us safely, but this is an awfully concerning matter. There’s no doubt the Proxia Empire played a part in the entire incident... but there’s a severe lack of definitive proof.” King Francois sighed with a stern frown.

“Yes. The mercenaries that appeared on our airship, in the Paladian village we were teleported to and at the Rubian fortress we visited, were all men with a connection to the Proxia Empire.”

Whenever an unpleasant task had to be done, disposable mercenaries were used to hide the identity of the kingdoms involved. This was a commonly used tactic, but being on the receiving end of it was a source of endless frustration.

Duke Huguenot raised his hand after a beat. “I have one thing to report regarding that.”

“What is it?” Christina asked.

“After Your Highnesses were abducted, your airship arrived at Rodania and caused an uproar. It was during this time that a man resembling Reiss, the ambassador from the Proxia Empire with known ties to Lucius, was spotted inside the central office. Celia was the one who reported this to me.”

Christina’s eyes widened in wonder, then glanced at Rio before asking after her well-being. “Professor Celia did that? Is she okay?”

Rio also seemed surprised and worried, as he had a stern look on his face.

“Yes. He apparently disappeared as soon as she spotted him.”

“I see.”

Christina, Flora, and Rio all sighed in relief.

“There’s the possibility she was mistaken, but if it really was him, he must have snuck into the central office with some kind of goal in mind. Unfortunately, that is the full extent of what I know, but it may be related to all of this,” Duke Huguenot said.

I’ll have to ask her what happened once I return to Rodania. Perhaps Aishia was the one who protected her. Rio imagined the situation and vowed to return as soon as possible.

“At any rate, we currently lack the evidence to accuse the Proxia Empire. The only place we can really pinpoint would be the Rubia Kingdom. Their actions have broken the alliance agreement with not only the Restoration, but our kingdom as well—their movements hereafter will be a source of interest to us,” Francois said with a cold smile, his anger simmering quietly.

The Rubia Kingdom’s actions were an act of rebellion not only towards the Restoration, but towards the Galarc Kingdom as well. It was a much more serious matter than just having their trust besmirched.

“The Restoration intends to officially protest the Rubia Kingdom’s actions,” Christina said.

“Galarc will also make an official objection towards the way our honorary knight and alliance princesses were treated,” Francois confirmed.

“So you’ll declare your concerns. Isn’t that pointless?” Hiroaki interrupted in a cynical tone.

“Yes, most likely so. The alliance is as good as broken already, so there’s a high chance they’ll ignore our objections,” Christina replied in a cool voice.

“Expressing your concerns while knowing that is just incompetence, isn’t it?” Hiroaki grumbled sullenly.

“Indeed, this could have immediately triggered a war under different circumstances. But unfortunately, Rubia is a minor kingdom located far from us. If we mobilized the army, we would have to traverse across the land of other kingdoms, and there isn’t that much to gain from occupying a minor kingdom like Rubia. Invasion would be an extremely inefficient means of retribution, great hero,” Francois said, admonishing Hiroaki with the magnanimity of a king.

“The Restoration as it is now doesn’t have the strength to invade such a distant kingdom either,” Christina added.

“But if you just sit around idly after expressing your concerns, the other side will just look down upon you,” Hiroaki grumbled persistently.

“Of course, we intend on retaliating in some form or another. Spreading word of the Rubia Kingdom’s actions to our neighboring allies is a given, but... Hmm...” Francois brought his hand to his chin and thought for a moment. When his eyes landed on Rio, he suddenly chuckled to himself. “What if we sent Haruto to go on a rampage in the Rubia Castle? No doubt they’d be struck with terror if the man who single-handedly helped the two princesses to escape from their grasp came back for retaliation.”

Rio froze, pressed for a reaction. “Surely you jest...”

“Hey! Don’t involve Haruto in any of your strange ideas, Your Majesty,” Satsuki said, immediately scolding Francois.

“I’m joking, of course. As king, not even I have the authority to mobilize Haruto.”

“Even if you had the authority, don’t do it. It’s way too dangerous.” Satsuki made sure to emphasize her point despite Francois’s chuckles.

“Hah. I don’t know about Proxia, but if you sent that guy to cause a scene in Rubia, they’d be the ones in danger,” Hiroaki scoffed, dampening the conversation.

“That... may not be that far from the truth, but Haruto will still be in danger. He’d be antagonizing himself if he did such a thing,” Satsuki said with a pout.

Christina was in agreement with Satsuki. “The Restoration wouldn’t possibly allow Sir Amakawa to do something so dangerous after being so indebted to him either.”

“Hmph...” Hiroaki snorted, unamused.

Charlotte looked at Rio while adding to the conversation in a humorous tone. “While I would personally love to witness Sir Haruto’s continued success, it’d be a problem if people start fearing him too much.”

“With all due respect, I believe everyone thinks too highly of me...” Rio stated hesitantly.

Just how does everyone see me?

From the sound of the conversation until now, they seemed to think he was capable of storming a royal castle by himself—and dealing severe damage to the other kingdom.

At that, the entire room blinked blankly back at him. It was as though they were all asking what he was getting at.

“Say, Liselotte,” Charlotte suddenly said.

“Yes, Your Highness?” Liselotte replied immediately.

“Sir Haruto’s first public appearance was before the monster attack on Amande, right?”

“If you’re referring to when I first met him, then that would be correct,” Liselotte said, nodding.

“Since then, Sir Haruto’s list of feats have extended beyond imagination. He subjugated a powerful minotaur and repelled the breath of a demi-dragon with his enchanted sword. He defeated the strongest knight of the Beltrum Kingdom and instilled fear into a five-thousand-man army of pursuing troops, forcing them to withdraw. On top of that, he’s now eliminated the infamous veteran mercenary, Lucius. Considering the number of these exploits, can you still claim that we’re overestimating you, Sir Haruto?”

Charlotte listed off Rio’s most prominent exploits, then turned to Rio with an elegant smile.

“It’s an honor to receive such praise, but when it comes to raiding a castle alone... I’m sure the Rubia Kingdom has its own formidable warriors,” Rio replied awkwardly.

If he prepared himself beforehand like when he rescued Celia from her wedding, he could potentially do it regardless of the strength of his opponents. However, that didn’t mean he could make such a public showing during times of peace. Rio wasn’t presumptuous enough to declare he could do it without any basis or knowledge of the opponent’s strength.

“If it’s renowned warriors of the Rubia Kingdom, then the first to come to mind is the Princess Knight, Princess Sylvie. However, from Princess Christina’s testimony, it doesn’t sound like Princess Sylvie could ever best Sir Haruto,” Charlotte pointed out.

“But there was a boy at the Rubian fortress who may be the fifth hero...” Rio reminded her of Kikuchi Renji, the boy he fought with at the fortress. Honestly speaking, not even Rio could grasp the true strength of the heroes.

“But you defeated that hero too, no?” Satsuki asked, cocking her head.

“I wouldn’t say I defeated him. I wanted to avoid getting too deeply involved, so I retreated before we could finish...”

After Rio answered Satsuki’s question, Hiroaki interrupted with a look of suspicion. “Was that guy really a hero?”

“Most likely. He had a halberd that could control ice, so I believe it was his Divine Arm.”

“Tch... A hero shouldn’t be losing so easily in battle. How pathetic.”

“You seem discontented by the hero’s defeat, but were you able to win against Haruto yourself?” Satsuki asked Hiroaki.

“Huh? Tch...” Hiroaki frowned. He opened his mouth to retort but recalled his past defeat against Rio and swallowed his words with a click of his tongue.

“How was the battle between the fifth hero and Sir Haruto in the eyes of you two?” Charlotte turned the conversation to Christina and Flora with a look of intense curiosity in her eyes.

Christina was the first to reply with an awkward glance at Rio’s expression. “Sir Amakawa took him on alongside the skilled mercenaries who were former subordinates of Lucius’s, but it looked to me like Sir Amakawa overwhelmed them from start to finish.”

“Yes, he was wonderful.” Flora nodded furiously, eyes sparkling as she replied.

“I’m sure it was an incredible sight. I wish I had been there to witness it—I’m so envious of you two.” Charlotte puffed up her cheeks and sighed sadly.

“Umm, you’d have to have been kidnapped to be there, Char.” Satsuki calmly pointed out the problem in her words.

“Bah. So envious indeed. Playing the hero more than actual heroes every single time...” Hiroaki grumbled bitterly. Roanna seemed to have overheard him, as she had a stiff expression beside him.

“We seem to have derailed the conversation a bit, but in all honesty, it would be more productive to have Haruto act alone than for me to increase military funding and have our army strike. But as I said before, I have no intention of doing such a thing.” With a wry smile and a hint of his true thoughts, Francois redirected the discussion back on topic.

“Damn right. Who cares about this guy’s great exploits or whatever. We were talking about what we’re gonna do to these Rubian guys for looking down on us, right?” Hiroaki immediately went along with Francois’s lead, not wanting to listen to praise for Rio anymore.

“If the fifth hero really is affiliated with the Rubia Kingdom, things become slightly complicated. For now, we’ll spread word of Rubia’s wrongdoing across other nations while requesting an explanation of the incident and the identity of the fifth hero. After that, we’ll consider imposing realistic and constructive sanctions—this should be the right course of action,” Francois explained.

“I agree with that. The Rubia Kingdom cannot be forgiven for this, but if they really have a hero on their side, we need to go through the correct procedure,” Christina expressed quietly.

“Indeed. That aside... I understand you were pursuing your longstanding enemy, but you did well rescuing Princess Christina and Princess Flora from their debacle, Haruto,” Francois said, looking at Rio in wonder.

Because Christina explained everything that had happened from her point of view, there was a lot of information missing about how Rio found the two of them. Thus, Francois was probably curious about that sequence of events as well.

“I obtained information on my journey suggesting that Lucius was in the Paladia Kingdom. After I made my way to the Paladian capital, I heard that First Prince Duran happened to be holding an event...” Rio explained briefly. Getting into too much detail would only complicate things, so he hid the fact he had snuck into the Proxia Castle and crossed swords with Emperor Nidoll Proxia.

“An event, you say?”

“It was a challenge where whoever could withstand one blow from Prince Duran was entitled to a reward. I decided to participate for the chance to ask about Lucius. I figured a renowned fighter like Prince Duran would have connections to a mercenary like him.”

“I see. And so you easily withstood the blow from Prince Duran,” Charlotte immediately assumed.

“That is correct. He told me where I could find Lucius—and that happened to be the village where the two princesses were.”

“Hmm. I find it questionable that he passed you that information, but... Prince Duran claimed the Paladia Kingdom wasn’t involved in the princesses’ kidnapping, right?” This was something Christina had mentioned earlier.

“How much do you actually believe in his words?” Francois asked.

“He was a rather difficult person to read, so I don’t trust him myself. However, I believe there is credibility to his claim that the Paladia Kingdom was not involved.”

“And why is that?”

“If Paladia had been involved in our abduction, there would be no need to teleport us to a shack in the middle of a deserted forest. They could have easily sent us to the Paladia Castle and confined us there.”

“That’s true. A very likely possibility. And thus, incomprehensible...”

“What do you mean...?” Christina seemed to sense something.

“Even if Paladia is unrelated to the abduction of Princess Christina and Princess Flora, the mercenary group behind everything is related to the Proxia Empire... And yet there is no clear motive here for Proxia.”

No one present noticed, but for a brief moment, something bitter flashed across Christina’s expression.

“What’s so incomprehensible about that, King Francois? I don’t quite get your point.”

Stop beating around the bush and get to the point—Hiroaki glared at Francois as though to say that. Francois continued without paying him any mind.

“If Lucius abducted the two princesses under the Proxia Empire’s order, he would have teleported them to the imperial castle instead of the Paladian forest. That would be the most secure way of confining them. There is a high risk of exposure when leaving them in a foreign nation—even temporarily—and he approached a foreign royal for help, although on a personal level. If Proxia ordered this, then Lucius was either unable to change the teleport destination from the Paladian forest, or he had some kind of goal in sending them to that forest in particular...” Francois offered his hypothesis under the premise of Lucius moving on the Proxia Empire’s orders. However, the incident this time just so happened to be unrelated—Christina and Flora were abducted purely for personal reasons.

Of course, there was a strong possibility they’d have been handed to the Proxia Empire afterwards, but the main purpose of abducting them had been to use them as hostages against Rio. It just so happened to have been Christina and Flora who were targeted, but Lucius would have been fine with anyone who had a connection to Rio. That line of thinking was giving Francois an odd feeling.

Meanwhile, Christina knew of this possibility already, but the guilt she felt for her former actions towards Rio made her purposefully divert the topic. “If the Proxia Empire hired Lucius’s group of mercenaries, then that would be in order to discard them after they completed the abduction,” she said.

“Indeed. It’s a typical method used to deny one’s involvement in various misdoings. I agree in regards to that point, but... Lucius’s information management seemed a little too poor for that. He sought cooperation from Prince Duran, who ended up revealing his location to Haruto. Haruto then arrived where the two princesses were. It’s almost as though he set things up to happen this way... Perhaps it was a setup?” Francois drew close to the heart of the matter, but he didn’t look entirely convinced about something.

“It is as you say. Lucius may have directed Prince Duran to inform me of his location in order for us to duel. The reason why Proxia’s motive is unclear is probably—no, it’s most certainly because of the existing connection between Lucius and myself,” Rio explained. He had asked Christina to hide this information beforehand, knowing that it could complicate matters. But now that things had come to this, he decided it would be better to bring it out into the open.

Meanwhile, Christina reacted to Rio’s words by pursing her lips in vexation.

“I had the same thought, but that wouldn’t make sense if Lucius didn’t know you were coming to Paladia beforehand, right? Unless Lucius witnessed you participating in Prince Duran’s event and decided to use the two princesses after...” Francois said, analyzing the situation with a doubtful expression.

“Wait, what are you saying? That Lucius bastard kidnapped Christina and Flora to use them as hostages to draw out Haruto? That means... Whoa, isn’t that pretty damn serious?”

Hiroaki had been listening to the discussion with a disinterested look until now, but he suddenly interrupted in a strangely lively voice. His expression had also perked up in interest.

“What’s so serious about it?” Christina asked with a sigh.

“Huh? Isn’t it obvious? It means you two were targeted because of this bastard here. That’s a grave matter,” Hiroaki said, pointing at Rio.

“You’re wrong,” Christina stated flatly.

“What? Why?”

“I believe we would have been abducted even if we didn’t have any connections to Sir Amakawa. In fact, Flora was once kidnapped in Amande before she was acquainted with Sir Amakawa, and I was also targeted by Reiss and Lucius’s subordinates on the way from Cleia to Rodania.”

Unconvinced, Hiroaki argued back. “Hold on. How can you be so sure Flora’s abduction in Amande had nothing to do with Lucius’s beef with Haruto? What if this bastard was the reason she was kidnapped back then as well?”

“I cannot think of any reason why Flora would be used as a hostage against Sir Amakawa.” Christina stood her ground without fearing Hiroaki’s position as hero.

“Hmm? That’s... Lucius had a personal grudge against the Beltrum Kingdom, right? If he kidnapped Flora because of that, he may have tried to use her as a hostage out of a similar grudge towards Haruto as well...” Hiroaki seemed to realize his reasoning was weak as he voiced it out loud, losing confidence and trailing off at the end.

“With all due respect, I believe that would be impossible once you factor in the situation back then,” Liselotte added to the conversation, denying Hiroaki’s thoughts.

Hiroaki paused for a long moment, then quietly turned to Liselotte and grumbled. “How come?” He didn’t like how she had interrupted just to defend Rio—especially when he wanted to avoid talking to her at all.

“It was a coincidence that Sir Haruto encountered Lucius back then,” Liselotte answered in her usual calm voice.

So she calls me “hero,” but this guy by his name.

It wasn’t particularly related to his suspicions towards Haruto, but Hiroaki thought that to himself anyway. The way Liselotte would call Haruto’s name at every opportunity had bothered him before, but now that she had rejected him, it was even more annoying to listen to.

“He could have just been lying about encountering Lucius by coincidence, though.” Hiroaki’s suspicion towards Rio didn’t end there. It was clear to everyone watching that he was being emotional and arguing based on his own conclusion.

“Princess Flora was present at the scene and testified that their conversation sounded like they hadn’t met in a while, so I doubt that...” It was impossible; suspecting that would mean accusing Flora of lying as well. Liselotte didn’t say that out loud, but she implied it with a glance at Flora as she spoke.

Flora immediately spoke up in defense of Liselotte’s explanation. “Yes. It definitely sounded like it was the first time in a while since Sir Haruto encountered the mercenary who tried to kidnap me. The other side wasn’t able to recall Sir Haruto right away, so there’s no mistaking it.”

The heck? Everyone keeps trying to stand up for this bastard... Now that I think about it, Flora keeps calling this guy “Sir Haruto” as well.

Flora had addressed Haruto in this way for a while now, but Hiroaki was more irritated by it now than he had ever been before. He wanted to stop the way they kept protecting him, but he didn’t have any material to argue with.

“Hmph. Fine, I guess. If you all insist.” Hiroaki finally backed down.

Francois, who had been watching quietly for a while, spoke up to give his opinion. “I too find it doubtful that Lucius would kidnap Princess Christina and Princess Flora only for the sake of his grudge against Haruto. It would be more reasonable to presume the Proxia Empire’s motives were included in the abduction.”

That being said, if this were true, the reason why Paladia was chosen as the teleport destination remains unclear... It’d be unproductive to discuss hypotheticals any further, so Francois chose not to state that out loud.

“Lucius held intense resentment for Haruto after the encounter in Amande. Is that correct?” Francois asked.

“He managed to flee after we were interrupted, but he was gravely wounded in Amande. That was most likely the reason,” Rio said.

“In that case, it all makes sense. Both the mercenary and his employer had motives invested in this. That’s why Princess Christina and Princess Flora were used as hostages. That must be it. Lucius already knew the two of them had some form of acquaintance with Haruto.”

“Yes. So without Sir Amakawa, Flora and I wouldn’t be here. We would have been imprisoned in the Proxia Castle right about now,” Christina said in summary of Francois’s understanding.

“Without a doubt.”

“It’s thanks to the connection between Lucius and Sir Amakawa that Flora and I were spared from further disaster. I can’t express my gratitude towards Sir Amakawa enough. When I already owe him more than I could ever return...” Christina said, a hint of a somber look on her face.

“Curious how he manages to appear at the most convenient moment every single time. It almost makes me wonder if he’s the one behind it all.”

Hiroaki decided to pick fault with the story and cast suspicion on Rio. His comment completely missed the mood of the room, making Roanna sweat nervously beside him.

“Sir Hiroaki,” Christina said with a sigh.

“Wh-What?”

“In order to protect us, Sir Amakawa was cornered in an extremely unfavorable position. I know this because I witnessed it myself, right up close. He was treading the line of life and death, yet he devoted himself to saving us.”

“So what?”

“So please refrain from making such rude remarks about him. I cannot overlook such comments, even if they come from the hero,” Christina stated firmly, fixing a critical stare at Hiroaki.

With no basis for his words, even Hiroaki knew he was being outright rude to Rio right now. He looked like he wanted to argue with Christina, but he ended up averting his gaze with a guilty look. “Fine. My bad. I’m not feeling well, so I’m gonna leave first.”

He swallowed down his protests and shot up to his feet.

“Go with Sir Hiroaki, Roanna,” Christina immediately ordered. Hiroaki was already walking towards the door.

“R-Right away.” Roanna got to her feet in a hurry, bowed, then left after Hiroaki.

“Damn it all.” There was no one around to hear Hiroaki’s muttering as he left by himself first. He had marched out of the door without so much as a glance back.

Roanna followed after him, and the door swung shut.

“I apologize for Sir Hiroaki’s impoliteness, Sir Amakawa,” Christina said with a rather regretful, pained look.

“There’s no reason for you to apologize,” Rio replied with a concerned smile.

“Just before the three of you arrived, the marriage discussion between Hiroaki and Liselotte was called off. That may be the reason for his bad mood,” Francois summarized with a light shrug.

“Sir Hiroaki and Lady Liselotte... I understand. No wonder everyone was gathered here.” Christina pressed a hand to her forehead as though she was holding back the onset of a headache.

“I am sorry,” Liselotte said, bowing her head awkwardly.

“It’s not something for you to apologize for either. In fact, I can imagine Sir Hiroaki was rather unreasonable about it. I’m sorry for all the trouble we’ve caused.” The look of fatigue in Christina’s expression only intensified.

Liselotte shook her head humbly. “Oh no, not at all.”

“At any rate, Princess Christina and Princess Flora have returned. Thanks to that, all of our immediate issues have been resolved. Let’s think of this in a positive way,” Francois said to the two of them.

“Okay.” Christina and Liselotte nodded together.

“The Proxia Empire backing Rubia’s betrayal is troubling, but is there anything else that needs attention?”

“That’s pretty much all the information we have... But if the Proxia Empire has someone who can freely use teleportation, it’d be quite the predicament,” Christina said.

“Hmm. Lost ancient sorcery that allows the manipulation of space. I’ve heard of its existence, but I’ve never witnessed it with my own eyes. I’d like to think it’s not easy to use, but...” Liselotte trailed off.

“We should be prepared for the worst-case scenario. I don’t know how freely they can control the teleport destination, but it’d be dangerous if they set it to their castle.”

“Indeed it would... For example, the banquet where we formally introduced Lady Satsuki to the public. We never ended up deducing the infiltration route the insurgents used, but if the Proxia Empire was involved in that raid, the incident can be explained through the use of teleportation,” Francois said.

“If that’s true, then it’s a terrifying thought.” Liselotte’s father, Cedric Cretia, uttered his sentiments after actively avoiding participation in the conversation until now.

“It is indeed...” Duke Huguenot imagined the use of teleportation in an attack on Rodania and agreed with sympathy in his voice.

Back then, I couldn’t detect any disturbance in magic essence from the use of teleport sorcery, Rio recalled. Any essence-detecting artifact would have picked up on it, and even people who can’t visualize essence can detect the disturbance after teleport is activated, if they have sharp senses. But... With an essence-blocking barrier, it might be possible to suppress the disturbance of ode and mana caused by teleport sorcery.

Amidst everyone else’s uneasiness, he used his familiarity with teleport sorcery to analyze whether it had been used.

“It’d also be most worrying if they could teleport directly into the room of someone important. Just the thought of that possibility gives me the chills,” Francois hummed with a grim look. The others must have imagined someone teleporting into their bedrooms as well, as their expressions were rather peaky.

“That shouldn’t be a problem,” Rio said to dispel their woes.

“Oh? And why is that?” Francois asked.

“In order to teleport with sorcery, the coordinates of the destination must be set in advance, so you cannot teleport anywhere you haven’t been before. It’s most likely done with a pair of artifacts—one to teleport the target and one to set the destination. If they wanted to teleport into the room of an important figure, they’d need to sneak into that room in advance to set the coordinates. Considering the difficulty of doing that, it’s more likely that they’ll choose an easier location to access.”

Francois’s eyes widened. “You’re oddly knowledgeable about this...” he commented in wonder.

“I heard about it from my benefactor, Lady Celia of Count Claire’s house. She said that it was described like this in ancient literature.”

The residents of the spirit folk village could use teleport sorcery, and Rio himself possessed artifacts with teleport sorcery embedded in them, but he naturally couldn’t tell them that here. That’s why he brought up Celia’s name to brush off answering.

Sorry, Celia.

“Celia Claire, the young sorcerer from Beltrum said to be a genius, you say? Then the information must be reliable.” When it came to the field of sorcery, Celia’s name was extremely persuasive. Francois hummed in awe.

“If the Proxia Empire was involved in the raid on the banquet, and if teleport sorcery was used for it, then someone in attendance may have collaborated with them to set the coordinates. If someone was there, it would be easy to set the coordinates to within the castle. For example...”

“Someone from the Rubia Kingdom, you think?” Francois considered the strong possibility of the Proxia Empire’s involvement and immediately suspected the Rubia Kingdom, seeing that they’d just betrayed them.

“Yes,” Rio nodded slowly.

“Indeed, if the Rubia Kingdom betrayed us as early as back then, things would make sense,” Francois said coldly, his anger intensifying. If the Proxia Empire possessed magic artifacts with teleport sorcery, Lucius using the same method made sense.

“If you are concerned that the artifact used to set the destination coordinates is still within the castle grounds, you should do a thorough investigation for any suspicious essence reactions. An artifact being used to set coordinates should emit a certain amount of magic essence.”

Though few in number, sorcerers that could use Zona Revelare—area search magic—could conduct the investigation, as could the similarly few artifacts capable of detecting essence reactions.

“I see. This has been a truly constructive discussion. There are artifacts capable of detecting suspicious essence in certain parts of the castle, but they only cover an extremely limited area. It’s a good chance there are artifacts there. Once we’re done here, I will have a search of the castle conducted and reevaluate the security.” Francois smiled, pleased to know that his fears of sudden invasion could be addressed.

“For reference, the magic artifact that teleported Flora and myself to Paladia was in the form of a crystal. But it’s possible the one set at the destination is in a different form,” Christina offered.

“I understand. Thank you for that information,” Francois said, nodding.

I should conduct a search around Amande as well. Maybe I should send someone back first to arrange that, Liselotte thought to herself. This information alone had been worth her trip here. In fact, at this moment, everyone in the room resolved themselves to thoroughly check their surroundings.

“Now then, I believe all that remains is to consider countermeasures against the forced teleportation that the princesses went through,” Francois said, moving on to the next topic.

“It’s likely that only a very small number of people can be teleported at once. Either the activation spell is chanted before the crystal is thrown at the target, or the caster teleports themselves while within a certain range of the person they want to drag along. If we take into account the time between chanting and spell activation, there should be a way of handling it if you react in time, but it may be quite difficult...” Christina explained, giving an accurate analysis based on when the teleport crystal was used on her.

“So you either distance yourself from the caster before they finish chanting, or you repel the crystal they throw back at them. It’s better than not knowing anything at all, I suppose. I shall pass that on to the security guards.”

“Yes. I pray that this kind of situation never happens again... The Restoration will also re-examine our security.”

“Indeed. I suppose that’s all there was to address for now... Now that we’ve exchanged all the necessary information, let’s talk about Haruto next,” Francois said, looking at Rio.

“Me?” Rio’s eyes widened at the sudden spotlight, and he tilted his head awkwardly.

“Yes. We need to discuss your reward.”

“I don’t require anything in particular...” Receiving things would only be a problem, so Rio tried declining respectfully. However...

“I will not allow it. Spare me your jests,” Francois said, bluntly shooting him down.

“I’m being serious...”

“What’s troubling is that in your case, you decline because of the bother rather than a lack of wants. Do you intend on retiring as a hermit at such a young age?” Francois lamented, pressing a hand to his forehead in worry.

“I’d prefer to live a quiet and peaceful life, if possible,” Rio admitted with a wry smile.

“As when I appointed you an Honorary Knight, it is my duty as king to properly reward your distinguished services. There will be no future for the kingdom if such meritorious deeds are not given proper recognition. Achievements must be rewarded in order. Failure to do so will only result in the best people leaving for greener pastures.”

“Of course, I am aware of that...”

It was a simple matter. By creating a custom where those who made achievements could expect to be appropriately recognized, the people serving the kingdom would work frantically to achieve greater heights. There weren’t many people who would work themselves to the bone for a nation that didn’t value them. A performance-based doctrine would create antagonism between those competing for recognition, but that could be managed with a properly established system.

A harsh truth for our kingdom, that not only failed to value him appropriately, but even charged him with a false accusation... Christina grimaced with bitter regret.

“So, accept your reward. The safe return of Princess Christina and Princess Flora is of immense benefit to Galarc as well. It’s more than enough cause for a reward. In fact, you are also owed a reward for escorting Princess Christina from Cleia to Rodania. You haven’t visited the castle since the banquet, so the incident is still unsettled.” Francois fixed his gaze on him.

“I am much obliged.”

“And so, I will be using this opportunity to reward you for everything—do be prepared.”

“Understood...” Rio nodded, head drooping.

Charlotte joined the conversation with a giggle. “Hee hee, Sir Haruto is so funny. You’re not meant to react to a reward with disappointment. But as father said, you don’t visit the castle often enough. That is unacceptable,” she protested, puffing up her cheeks at Rio with a sulking look.

“My apologies. I was traveling around from place to place,” Rio replied, shrinking back.

“Yet you had a meal with Lady Satsuki and Liselotte?” Charlotte immediately pointed out, causing Rio to struggle for words.

“That’s...”

“Stop tormenting him, Charlotte. We’re discussing the matter of rewards right now,” Francois said, intervening.

“I understand. We can leave this topic for later, when we can go over it in detail.” Charlotte immediately backed down, shooting a suggestive and bewitching smile at Rio.

Rio looked at Satsuki for help but was met with a shrug of resignation.

“The Restoration would also like to reward you,” Christina said apologetically, having sensed Rio’s predicament.

“I have already received an estate in Rodania from the Restoration, so I would not feel comfortable accepting anything further...”

Of course, that wasn’t acceptable.

“I’ve witnessed the making of many commendable feats from my position, but none have been as notable as yours, Haruto. Your many achievements have saved the Restoration time and time again. If we do not reward you for it, we risk the spread of negative rumors. Please accept our gratitude as well,” Duke Huguenot said cheerfully on Christina’s behalf, who wasn’t as persuasive.

“I understand...” Rio agreed reluctantly.

“Speaking of which, you have a mansion in Rodania?”

“Yes. I received one the other day.”

“Hmm. It’d be odd for you to have a place in Rodania, but not in Galarc. I shall give you one of the royal family’s mansions within the castle grounds,” Francois declared.

Christina, Liselotte, Duke Cretia and his wife, and Duke Huguenot—all seasoned members of the noble class and above—all looked clearly shocked, which was a rare expression on them. Only Charlotte was left smiling triumphantly.

“A mansion within the castle grounds? I don’t believe I’ve ever seen any nobles living within the grounds...” Rio said, looking at the others.

“Of course not. The castle and its land belong to the royal family, after all. While guests may stay at the castle, long-term residence of those outside of royalty is not permitted. Not even Cedric—Duke Cretia, the leading noble of this kingdom—has an estate on the castle grounds. Duke Huguenot’s mansion in the Beltrum capital would have been outside of the castle grounds too,” Francois said, looking at Duke Cretia and Duke Huguenot.

Incidentally, many of the influential nobles who served as lords of territories loaned from the kingdom wanted to assume important positions within the royal castle. In fact, it was because they were influential that they wanted to do so. This was because in centralized nations such as Galarc or the Beltrum Kingdom, participation in the kingdom’s governance could only be done from the center—that is, the royal castle.

Thus, it was customary for nobles to have secondary homes in the noble district of the capital, separate from their main residence in their territory. The distance of the mansion to the castle and the extravagance of the estate also became a status symbol for those working in the castle. It was common for the head of a family to leave their territory’s management to an heir and spend most of the year in the capital to work at the castle.

“In that case, I believe it should be impossible for me to possess a mansion within the castle grounds when I’m not even a duke...” Rio said hesitantly, probing for Francois’s true intentions.

“That’s because this is a one-of-a-kind privilege unavailable to the other nobles of the kingdom. I’m sure many would be flabbergasted to hear about this,” Francois said, grinning.

“That’s a little too much... Wouldn’t a mansion outside of the castle suffice? There shouldn’t be any reason for it to be within the castle grounds...”

The king himself was basically declaring his favoritism for Rio over other nobles—an action that would only attract unwanted attention. Thus, Rio wished to decline the offer.

“Oh, I figured it’d be easier for Lady Satsuki to come and go freely if it were within the castle grounds. The procedure to leave the castle can be quite troublesome, so it would remove that hassle completely. Lady Miharu can also stay for as long as she pleases the next time she visits the castle. Isn’t it a wonderful idea?”

“That certainly would be convenient...” Satsuki mumbled.

Francois smiled at that. “There’s no need to worry about the backlash from the nobles either. They’ll have no choice but to hold their tongues once they hear about your list of achievements. If we consider it a reward for both escorting Princess Christina to Rodania and the incident this time, it seems reasonable. Wouldn’t you agree, Cedric?”

“Indeed, they would fall silent... But envious people will also appear. The nobles working in the royal court in particular may feel discontent. Such people would form cliques to spread malicious gossip. Wouldn’t it be better for Haruto to avoid creating enemies in the royal court?” Duke Cretia gave his honest opinion with Rio in mind.

“Those who envy his achievements will appear no matter what, but we may be able to do something to decrease those numbers. It’s the same as the usual power struggle that goes on in the castle—it all boils down to who you ally with.”

“I completely agree...”

“With myself, Cedric, and Lady Satsuki ironclad on Haruto’s side, most people will be silenced in fright. All that’s left is to give it a final push. If I move myself, it’ll be a clear act of pressure... You understand?”

Make sure you pull the strings in your own faction to get a good word in—that was what Francois was implicitly ordering Cedric to do. In other words, he had to increase the number of Haruto’s allies in the royal court—an incredibly vital task.

“As I thought...” Cedric nearly hung his head.

“I’m leaving it to you. Understand?”

Cedric immediately found his resolve and nodded respectfully. “Yes, Your Majesty. I owe Haruto for saving my daughter in Amande, so I shall get on it right away.”

“So there you have it, Haruto.”

“I’m not sure I wanted to learn all that...” Rio’s face twitched faintly as he caught a peek at the inner workings of a vertically structured society.

“I grant you a mansion on the royal castle grounds. This is officially decided as of now.”

“I gratefully accept...” Rio bowed his head lightly at Francois’s smiling declaration.

“Even the unused mansions are regularly maintained, so it should be possible to hand it over immediately. You may need permanent servants for the mansion, but... The staff selection must be meticulous, to prevent anyone suspicious from slipping in. If you wish to do this yourself, that can also be arranged,” Christina explained.

“What will you do?” Francois asked Rio.

“I don’t believe there’s any need to hire permanent servants. I can look after myself, and I’m not used to living together with servants anyway.”

“I see... Let me know if you change your mind. We can also prepare temporary staff on our end for your needs,” said Francois.

“I am very thankful for your consideration.”

“That will be all for the reward from our kingdom. What will the Restoration do?” Francois asked Christina.

“The Restoration will require a little more time to decide what to reward Sir Amakawa with. We need to spend more time considering what we can offer that will be worthy of Sir Amakawa’s services.”

“I see. Is that fine with you, Haruto?”

“Of course,” Rio nodded.

“Then let’s call it a day here. There are various things I need to discuss with Cedric. If you wish to continue amongst yourselves, feel welcome to,” Francois said, expressing his intention to leave.

“Lady Satsuki and I can take over entertaining Sir Haruto from here,” Charlotte immediately suggested.

“I would be honored.” Rio nodded readily.

Francois paused just before he left and asked, “Speaking of which, what are your plans now, Haruto?”

“I’d like to visit Lady Celia, so I’m thinking of going back to Rodania with Princess Christina and the others. I also have to return to Miharu and our other housemates...”

If he was receiving a mansion, that would probably have to wait for later. However, Rio personally wanted to leave as soon as possible.

“Flora and I have to show ourselves to the organization to reassure the others of our safety, so we were thinking of leaving as early as tomorrow...” Christina explained.

“Huh? You only just got here and you’re going to leave already?” Charlotte expressed her displeasure with a sullen pout. Then she clapped her hands together, as though she just came up with a brilliant idea. “I know! You can bring everyone to the castle. Since you have your own mansion here now.”

Rio was taken aback by the suggestion, but hummed after hesitating for a moment. “Many of them are unfamiliar with noble society, so bringing them here is a bit...”

Celia and Aishia were living in Rodania, while Miharu, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma were living in the outskirts. If he invited them all to the castle, the only ones who would accept for sure would be Celia and Miharu.

I haven’t spent much time with everyone in the stone house—especially Latifa—since we came to the Strahl region, so I want to stay with them for a while.

He didn’t like the thought of separating everyone after coming this far either.

“But Lady Satsuki must want to see Lady Miharu again too, and wouldn’t Lady Miharu want to see Lady Satsuki as well?” Charlotte asked.

“Well, I’d love to do that if possible, but...” Satsuki agreed, but she didn’t demand anything out of consideration for Rio’s circumstances.

“If it’s merely a matter of being unfamiliar with noble society, don’t worry. They can just stay within Sir Haruto’s mansion. Father may want to meet them, but I can use my authority to refuse all other meetings with anyone else.”

It seemed that Charlotte was fully prepared to use her authority in order to entice Rio. Rio smiled somewhat wryly at that realization.

I want to let Miharu and Satsuki meet up as well. If we can keep Latifa’s contact with the others in this castle to a bare minimum, then perhaps it may be worth inviting them anyway.

“Fine. I cannot promise I’ll bring them for sure, but I’ll ask everyone what they think.”

“I will eagerly await their reply,” Charlotte said joyfully, her movements full of charm.

“Hmm. If you’re leaving tomorrow, it would be best to hand over the mansion today. Charlotte, you know the empty mansion beside the tower Lady Satsuki is residing in?” Francois asked.

“Yes, father. Is that the mansion you’re granting to Sir Haruto?”

“Indeed. You can show Haruto the way with Lady Satsuki. The key is in my office, so come with me.”

“I understand. I’ll be back soon, so please wait here, Lady Satsuki, Sir Haruto. Liselotte, you stay here too. Come with us to see Sir Haruto’s mansion later.”

“Yup, okay,” Satsuki said.

“If it isn’t a bother, then gladly,” Liselotte added.

“Also, since father has things to discuss with Duke Cretia, would you like to join us on the tour, Lady Julianne?” Charlotte asked, inviting Liselotte’s mother along.

As a duchess, Julianne was of a lower status than the royal Charlotte, but Charlotte spoke to her with respect considering their age difference.

“I would be delighted to, if it’s not a problem for anyone else.”

“You’re more than welcome to come along. Isn’t that right, Sir Haruto?”

“Of course,” Rio replied immediately. He wouldn’t have been able to decline due to his position, but he’d spoken to Julianne when he was last here for the banquet and wanted to thank her once again for that, so he had no reason to refuse.

“Then it’s decided.” Charlotte smiled happily. Thus, it was decided that the Galarc side of the room would head with Rio to see his new mansion.

Meanwhile, having constantly been with Rio for some time now, Flora watched them all with a somewhat lonely, envious look.

Charlotte seemed to notice Flora’s expression. “Would you like to come along, Princess Christina, Princess Flora? I would love to hear more about what happened on your journey with Sir Haruto.”

“We...”

What should they do? Was it okay to go? Out of consideration for Rio, Christina trailed off, leaving a slight pause. She looked at Flora beside her, who had a very eager expression on her face.

“Since you’ve offered, we will go too,” Christina replied humbly.

“In that case, I shall prepare a change of clothes for you two, so please follow me. We can’t have you dressed in that travel attire forever.”

Christina and Flora had been led to this room directly after their journey, so Charlotte made a proposal out of consideration for them.

“Thank you very much,” Christina said first. Flora echoed her words.

“I’ll have Sir Haruto’s clothing brought to the mansion for you to change once we arrive.”

“I’d appreciate that.”

Rio was similarly in his travel clothes. He had a change of clothes in the Time-Space Cache, but Charlotte was unaware of its existence. However, Rio didn’t have many clothes suitable for a noble to wear, so he was grateful for the consideration.

“Such is the plan. We’ll find you later, Duke Huguenot,” Christina said.

“Understood. I will go check on Sir Hiroaki, then.”

Duke Huguenot bowed his head smoothly.

◇　◇　◇

After their discussion, King Francois, Second Princess Charlotte, Duke Cretia, Christina, Flora, and Duke Huguenot exited the room, leaving Rio, Satsuki, Liselotte, and Julianne behind. They were to wait until Christina and Flora finished changing and Charlotte returned with the key to Rio’s mansion.

“I haven’t spoken to you since the night of the banquet. Since I haven’t given a proper greeting yet, I’d like to do that now. It’s nice to see you again,” Satsuki said to Julianne. She had exchanged greetings with countless nobles at the banquet, but she clearly remembered Liselotte’s mother.

Julianne smiled at Satsuki. “Yes. It’s an honor to be remembered by the great hero.”

“Why, that’s because you are so beautiful. As expected of Liselotte’s mother... In fact, I first thought you two were sisters with a slight age gap, so I was shocked when I heard you were actually parent and child. That really left an impression.”

“Why, I’m so flattered to hear that the great hero thinks that of me.” Julianne blushed shyly.

“I’m not really accustomed to being referred to as ‘hero.’ Please call me by my name.”

“Then, if you do not mind... Lady Satsuki. Thank you for getting along with my daughter,” Julianne said, tipping her head.

“No no, I should be saying that—Liselotte’s looked after me so much,” Satsuki replied sociably, returning the bow.

“Her work as a governor and head of a trading company has caused her to neglect interaction with her peers, so I am most appreciative of you becoming her friend,” Julianna said, showing a glimpse of her parental affection.

Liselotte had a faint blush on her face. “Isn’t that enough, mother?”

“Hee hee. Don’t worry about that. Liselotte and I have become great friends. She always visits me when she comes to the capital for business. Thank you, Liselotte.” Satsuki giggled, expressing her appreciation.

“Not at all. Talking with you also makes me happy, so I should be the one thanking you.”

Seeing her beloved daughter’s bashful reply, Julianne addressed her gently. “How wonderful, Liselotte.”

“Yes, mother,” Liselotte agreed in an energetic voice.

“Please forgive my delayed greeting. Thank you for your help the last time we met, Lady Julianne. Lady Liselotte as well.” Rio joined the conversation, greeting Julianne and Liselotte. Since they were in front of the king earlier, all their greetings had been abridged.

“The pleasure was mine. It’s been a while, Sir Haruto,” Liselotte replied first.

“It’s a joy to be able to speak to you again properly, Sir Amakawa. Thank you for inviting me to see your mansion along with Lady Satsuki and my daughter,” Julianne responded, smiling in true delight.

“Don’t mention it. My journey has left me with little time to meet with everyone, so I’m glad we’ve been blessed with this opportunity to chat. I wanted to thank you once again.”

“It’d be nice if you showed your face around here more often now that you’ve got a mansion,” Satsuki playfully requested.

“I intend on doing so in the future. You can think of it as your own home and come and go freely while I’m here.”

“You’ve said it now. I’m looking forward to it.” Satsuki beamed, fully intending on taking him up on his word.

“Yes,” Rio said, nodding with a welcoming smile.

“It’s decided! Now I’m even more curious to see what your new mansion will look like. Thanks, Haruto.”

“I’ve done nothing worth thanking me for.”

“That’s not true. Your distinguished service is what prompted this mansion as a reward, so if you hadn’t returned safely with Princess Christina and Princess Flora, I wouldn’t have something to look forward to this much. They’re ordinary words, but it doesn’t feel right not to say them... So, thanks. I’ll take you up on your kind offer and visit you every day you’re here,” Satsuki said, dispelling the gloomy atmosphere with an impish giggle at the end of her words.

“I see,” Rio said, chuckling.

“Do either of you know what kind of mansion he’s going to get?” Satsuki asked the two members of the Cretia family.

“I know which building His Majesty was referring to. It’s a very beautiful mansion, fit for royal inhabitants. It was also constructed recently, so it’s a modern and stylish design. However, its location is normally restricted to royalty, so its interior design is a mystery to me... Would you know, mother?” Liselotte answered first, then turned to Julianne.

“I haven’t been inside either, so I’m brimming with curiosity as well,” Julianne said, exuding delight.

“I feel the same way. Seeing the layout and interior design of other homes is so exciting.”

Thus, their animated conversation continued until Charlotte returned half an hour later with Christina and Flora in their fresh sets of clothes.

Chapter 2: New Place, New Ripples?

Roughly half an hour later, the group had relocated from the drawing room to the grounds of the castle. Charlotte led the way to the mansion Francois had bestowed onto Rio, and they were accompanied by Satsuki, Liselotte, Julianne, and a freshly changed Christina and Flora.

“This is the mansion that Sir Haruto was given,” Charlotte said, coming to a stop in front of the building to point it out.

“It’s a stone’s throw away from the tower I’m living in. I figured it was within eyeshot of my room, but I wasn’t sure exactly where. It looks even better up close, though.”

Satsuki turned around to look up at the tower she lived in. There were fewer than one hundred meters between the two buildings.

“Let’s go inside. It has some basic furnishings and was restocked with supplies while you were all waiting, so you can move in right away. I’ll give you a brief tour of all the rooms, and then we can have a chat in the drawing room. Come this way.”

Charlotte resumed leading the way. Several of her attendants were waiting before the mansion, bowing their heads silently. One of them looked up and walked over to the entrance to open the door.

The party proceeded to enter the mansion. They first went through every room, allowing Rio to change his clothes along the way, then finally moved to the drawing room to sit down on the sofa there.

The seating was based on Charlotte’s casual lead—Liselotte and Julianne sat in the lower seats closest to the door, with the others diagonally on either side of them in a U-shape. Rio was sandwiched between Satsuki and Charlotte, while Christina and Flora sat across from them.

“As expected of a royal mansion... It’s wonderful. There’s so much space, and there are so many rooms,” Satsuki said, impressed by the tour she’d just experienced.

“I still have my doubts about living here when I’m not royalty...” Rio muttered, giving his thoughts once again now that he had seen the mansion.

“Yeah, being the only one exempted to live on the castle grounds does kind of stand out,” Satsuki said, smiling wryly out of sympathy for Rio.

But Charlotte immediately beamed. “If the king that reigns over all royalty has allowed it, then there isn’t a problem at all. I too would love to have you live in this mansion, so I’ll support you to the best of my ability.”

“Aha ha...” Satsuki laughed dryly. “There’s one thing I’ve been wondering. What is defined as ‘royalty’? I know Char is a royal, and so are Princess Christina and Princess Flora, but how far down the bloodline can you go before the relatives are no longer considered royalty? It’s never been made clear to me, so I thought there were lots of royals.”

“That’s actually explained in detail in the Royal House Law. Every child born between the current king and his first wife that hasn’t renounced their royal status is considered royal—this is the same for every kingdom. It’s also common to include the previous king and his first wife, as well as the children between them. Apart from that, it tends to vary from kingdom to kingdom,” Charlotte explained, recalling the facts from her memory. She then turned to one of the other princesses in the room. “Is that how it works in the Beltrum Kingdom, Princess Christina?”

Christina nodded and spoke with a calm tone. “Yes, the same applies there.”

“In other words, regardless of their current or former post, whoever has a history of being the king and queen is considered royal for their entire lives. And their children will also keep being royals as long as they don’t renounce their status,” Satsuki said, summarizing the explanation to make it easier to understand.

“Yes, exactly. Renunciation is the complete withdrawal from the royal family. There are special exceptions when a foreign royal family is involved, but in most cases, marrying into the family of a vassal means taking on their status instead. It’s quite common for royals to marry into the duke families of the kingdom. In fact, a royal has married into the Cretia house in the past,” Liselotte continued, looking at Satsuki.

“Hmm... So you’re not royalty, but a relative to royalty. I see, I see.”

“Indeed.”

“Come to think of it, I don’t see any royals outside of the king’s direct descendents in the castle very often. I have greeted them before, though.”

“It isn’t desirable for other royals to involve themselves in politics, as it can potentially cause the decentralization of power. That’s why the only ones allowed to live inside the castle are father, mother, and us children—Michel, Rosalie, and myself. Everyone else lives in mansions within the castle grounds.”

“If you don’t mind me asking out of curiosity, is the reason a royal would marry a vassal and renounce their status also politically motivated?” Satsuki looked at Charlotte.

“Yes, it is. Most are made under the pretense of strengthening the royal family’s bond with a particular vassal. Since the difference in status always ends up hindering things, it’s common to marry into the vassal’s family, as I said before,” Charlotte explained, sending a quick, flirtatious glance at Rio before giggling.

“Hmm... I see...” Satsuki also glanced at Rio and nodded in understanding.

“At any rate, renunciation mostly applies to royals of low succession rank, so for those with high ranks like Princess Christina, Princess Flora, and myself, it’s not a matter of concern,” Charlotte added.

“Mm... But isn’t it difficult to find a marriage partner without renouncing your status? Will high-ranked royals end up single for their whole lives?”

“That won’t happen. For the high-ranked royals, it’s common to let the children of their vassals marry into the royal family instead. But it’s mostly the duke families that do so.”

“Ah, so they can marry while maintaining their royal status. I see.”

“It isn’t always the case, but it’s seen as disgraceful for a high-ranked royal to renounce their royal status. Even if they don’t admit it out loud, there are royals who wish to keep their status for their entire lives.”

In other words, there was a hierarchy within royalty, and whether one was renounced depended on that ranking—and high-ranked royals abhorred the idea of renouncing their status.

“I think I get it now... Royal marriage sure is complicated, huh?” Satsuki’s face twitched faintly as she processed all the information she’d just received.

“Indeed it is,” Charlotte sighed tiredly, but with strong agreement. She then turned to Rio next to her and smiled gracefully. “But if it were for Sir Haruto, I would happily renounce my royal status.”

Rio had just brought his cup to his mouth, but those words took him by surprise, causing him to choke. “A-Ahem... Pardon me,” he said as soon as he recovered, still flustered.

But everyone else present was frozen in disbelief at Charlotte’s statement, so his words never reached them.

The first one to speak among them was Satsuki. “H-Hey now, Char. You shouldn’t say that in front of Princess Christina and Princess Flora, yeah?” she warned her.

“That’s not necessarily true. The situation has changed from the time when Sir Haruto left the castle after the banquet ended.”

“What do you mean...?” Satsuki asked, watching Charlotte carefully for any change in expression. She recalled the bomb that was dropped after Rio left the castle.

It’s true that I considered him to be an older brother, but it turns out I was mistaken. It seems I’ve started to harbor a liking for Sir Haruto personally, Satsuki thought.

“I’m saying that it’s all thanks to Sir Haruto. Hee hee. We weren’t able to meet for a while, but you didn’t forget about me, right?” Charlotte evaded Satsuki’s question and spoke to Rio directly.

“No, of course not...” Rio replied awkwardly under her gaze, clearly remembering what had happened at the time.

“I’m so pleased.” Charlotte was delighted, beaming in a carefree and innocent way.

Meanwhile, Liselotte watched her as though she was seeing something truly curious. As a duke’s daughter, Liselotte had known Charlotte from a young age, and since Charlotte had also taken a liking to her, they’d ended up becoming good friends. They knew each other well.

It wasn’t rare for Charlotte to show interest in the opposite sex, but it was normally for the purpose of teasing them. She had never been serious about it. In other words, teasing the opposite sex and enjoying their reactions was one of her few hobbies—and an extremely troublesome one, at that. That had been the case until now, but...

This expression... Is Princess Charlotte serious?

It seemed like this time was different; the look on Charlotte’s face was like nothing Liselotte had ever seen before. And as far as Liselotte knew, Charlotte had never made any direct statements to signify a special liking in the opposite sex. She merely pretended to like them.

If she would happily renounce her royal status for him, that means... She wants to marry him...? I-I don’t know. What happened between the two of them? What does this mean? I’m so curious, but...

Liselotte was helplessly interested in Charlotte’s intentions. A rare look of surprise remained on her face; Julianne saw that look from beside her and giggled.

Charlotte leaned in close to Rio beside her. “And so, I wish to see you again soon. I won’t stop you from going to Rodania with Princess Christina and Princess Flora, but please do what you must to persuade everyone, then return quickly. I am also very curious about this Lady Celia person who is so close to you.”

“She is a part of the Restoration, so I cannot bring her with me at my own discretion... She also has work to do in Rodania right now,” Rio answered, faltering.

“Then let’s ask Princess Christina for permission. What do you say, Princess Christina?” Charlotte asked her on the spot. Her handling of the situation was extremely nimble—almost as though she had planned this from the moment she invited Christina along. This behavior would have been exceedingly rude depending on the status and position of those involved, but that didn’t apply to her as a high-ranked royal.

Christina agreed readily without any hesitation. “That should be fine. It’s almost time for a long vacation, so it won’t be particularly difficult to cut short her work as a lecturer. I’m sure she’d like to spend some time with Sir Amakawa as well.”

“Then it’s decided!” Charlotte rejoiced with an exceedingly sweet smile. “Lady Celia and Sir Haruto seem rather close, so I’m truly looking forward to meeting her... That’s right! If Lady Miharu and any others are coming to stay, we should hold a sleepover in this mansion.”

“You all right with that, Haruto? You don’t have to agree if you don’t want to, okay? At this rate, Char will keep deciding on everything,” Satsuki said to Rio, sighing tiredly. She probably had to put up with this kind of pushiness on a daily basis.

“I’ll decide after asking everyone what they think.”

They’ll also have to consider that while deciding whether to come... Rio thought, but he kept that to himself as he replied with a rather strained smile.

“Then we’ll have a sleepover if they all come! It’s a rare opportunity, so you should come too, Liselotte.”

“Me? I have my work schedule to consider, so it might be difficult for me...” Liselotte was taken aback by the sudden offer.

“Sir Haruto is leaving for Rodania with Princess Christina and the others tomorrow, right? How long will it take for you to return to Galtuuk?”

“Let’s see... We should arrive within the day if we take the enchanted airship from Galtuuk to Rodania, and I can speak to Lady Celia immediately... I’d need another one or two days to meet up with Miharu and the others, so if I can catch an airship back to Galtuuk, then perhaps a week or so?” Rio pondered, giving himself plenty of leeway. Since he was in front of others, he used a title when referring to Celia.

“You can leave your return trip to me. I’ll send out the airship,” Christina offered.

“Oh, are you sure? I was prepared to send one of ours to fetch him,” Charlotte said.

“Yes. I intend on returning soon to speak with King Francois, so I’d be grateful if Sir Amakawa is willing to accompany me on the trip.”

“I see. Then the transport will be left to the Restoration. If you’re coming back with Sir Haruto, would you like to participate in the sleepover too, Princess Christina?” Charlotte said with a giggle.

“Oh, no, I...” As before, her reservation towards Rio took precedence. Christina was about to reject the invitation by reflex when she suddenly noticed Flora’s expectant gaze on her and swallowed her words.

“If Princess Christina is in attendance, then Princess Flora is more than welcome as well,” Charlotte added with a glance at Flora.

Christina replied after a moment of hesitation. “I’m not sure if we’ll be able to participate in a sleepover, but we could attend a tea party or dinner together.”

“Wonderful! There’s even more to look forward to with the two of you there. But we don’t want Sir Haruto’s companions to feel uncomfortable, so there’ll be no formalities or any standing on ceremony—please keep that in mind,” Charlotte said, showing ample consideration for Miharu and the others as well.

Things really do keep getting more grand. Is it even acceptable for unmarried princesses and noblewomen to stay in a man’s house? It may be too late for me to ask now, though, Rio thought in dubious confusion.

“Oh, I’m so looking forward to it. If only the day could arrive faster.” Charlotte had a truly satisfied look on her face as she lost herself in her thoughts. The event was probably happening for sure in her mind.

I guess my participation is set as well... Well, I want to let Miharu see Satsuki again, and I’ll have to be there even if Latifa and the others can’t come. As for the sleepover... Well, I can just shut myself in my room as much as possible...

If Charlotte was the organizer for everything, then Rio’s fears would probably be of no concern. Any further contemplation would only add to his worries, so he decided not to think anymore.

“How about you, Lady Julianne?” Charlotte asked.

“I’m married already, so you young people should enjoy yourselves. I’ll inform my husband, so please look after my daughter,” Julianne declined with a cheerful spring in her voice.

Liselotte sighed quietly. Looks like my participation in all this is decided, huh? I’ll have to adjust my schedule once I return to Amande.

However, there was a faint smile on her face.

◇　◇　◇

The conversation that took place in Rio’s new mansion was generally friendly, but at the request of Charlotte, who wished to save the detailed discussion for the sleepover, they decided to call it a day a little over an hour later. Satsuki, Charlotte, Liselotte, and Julianne were to remain in Rio’s mansion.

“Well then, Flora and I will be leaving now.”

Christina and Flora prepared to leave. They had heard the story of how Liselotte’s engagement talks with Hiroaki went down earlier, so they probably wanted to talk to Duke Huguenot and Hiroaki about it in further detail.

“Could you show us the way to Duke Huguenot’s room,” Christina asked the lady-in-waiting as soon as she left Rio’s mansion. With her guards included, a total of ten odd people moved across the grounds and towards Duke Huguenot’s room.

“Duke Huguenot isn’t here right now. According to the guard, he’s currently visiting the hero’s room...”

Duke Huguenot was absent from the room the Galarc Kingdom had assigned to him. The lady-in-waiting had exchanged words with the guard beside his room to find out his current location.

Christina thought for a moment before deciding to visit Hiroaki’s room. “I see... Can you lead us there?” she requested.

“Understood.”

The lady-in-waiting bowed her head respectfully and began leading the way. It was right near Duke Huguenot’s room, so they arrived in less than a minute. Thus, Christina and Flora entered the room.

“Greetings, Princess Christina, Princess Flora.”

There were three figures inside: Hiroaki, Duke Huguenot, and Roanna. Duke Huguenot and Roanna stood up to welcome them, bowing their heads. Their expressions were slightly panicked.

Hiroaki was sitting on the sofa with a sullen look on his face. That was enough for Christina and Flora to presume he was in a bad mood.

“Good day, Sir Hiroaki.” Christina paid him no mind as she pinched the hem of her dress and curtseyed, greeting him calmly.

“Huh? It hasn’t been a good day for me,” Hiroaki snapped sarcastically.

“Did something happen?” Christina asked, still calm.

“No... Nothing. So you two were off having fun with that Haruto bastard, huh?” Hiroaki turned away with a huff, sulking.

“It was an invitation from Princess Charlotte, the princess of our ally kingdom that Sir Haruto, our savior, is affiliated with. We cannot treat them with disdain.”

“You say that, but you two actually wanted to be there, didn’t you?” Hiroaki muttered under his breath. However, his words failed to reach anyone’s ears.

“Did you say something?” Christina tilted her head.

Hiroaki grit his teeth. “I was in the middle of talking to Duke Huguenot and Roanna,” he began to say.

“What were you talking about?” Christina asked, seeking clarification.

“About my marriage to Rosalie.”

Christina glanced at Duke Huguenot and Roanna, who looked rather pale, then turned back to Hiroaki. “Just to confirm, this is Third Princess Rosalie of the Galarc Kingdom you’re referring to. Is that correct?”

“Yeah.”

“I see. Please let me hear the details. You may all sit down as well.”

Sensing something troublesome on the horizon, Christina prompted her party to sit down before taking a seat opposite to Hiroaki herself. Flora sat beside her, the two of them facing Hiroaki. Duke Huguenot and Roanna moved to a lower seat.

“What’s the story?” Christina asked Hiroaki once they had settled into their seats.

“There’s not much to tell. I want Rosalie as my first wife. That’s all,” Hiroaki said simply, lifting his face to watch her reaction.

“I see. Were Duke Huguenot and Roanna explaining why that would be impossible?” Christina asked in a detached tone, showing no particular surprise as she let Hiroaki stare at her.

“...Yeah.” The unexpected reaction made Hiroaki’s brow furrow faintly as he nodded.

“You originally agreed to Flora as a first wife. Is that correct? This was announced publicly.”

“But Flora disappeared with no way of knowing if she was alive. The engagement was as good as called off at that point. That’s why I was getting engaged to Rosalie to prevent the organization from falling apart,” Hiroaki replied in an overeager manner.

“You are entirely correct. However, Flora returned alive before things proceeded with the engagement, so the Galarc Kingdom would also be expecting you to return to Flora. I believe your engagement with Princess Rosalie has been called off at this point.”

“Well, how convenient for you. I’m getting fed up with having my engagement change at the drop of a hat, you know?”

A conflicted look flashed across Christina’s face before she bowed her head solemnly. “Indeed, that is most understandable. I apologize for sweeping you along at our convenience.”

“Hmph.” Hiroaki snorted, finding some satisfaction in that response.

“There’s one thing I’d like to ask. Is the reason you feel so strongly about marrying Princess Rosalie because you love her?”

At Christina’s question about his feelings for Rosalie, Hiroaki’s eyes darted everywhere in a sudden show of embarrassment. “H-Huh? Oh, not really... If anything, I’m neutral about it.”

“That was imprudent of me. However, it is something crucial for me to know... I apologize for my rudeness.” Christina apologized once again.

Hiroaki looked suspicious. “Huh...?”

“Allow me to confirm one last thing. You wish for Princess Rosalie to be your first wife, not Flora. Is that correct?” Christina continued, staring at him.

“Y-Yeah. That’s what I was saying from the beginning.” Pressured by Christina’s gaze, Hiroaki’s answer came out in a high-pitched squeak.

“I understand. Then let’s call off your engagement to Flora,” Christina stated simply.

“Wh-What are you saying, Princess Christina?!” Duke Huguenot was unusually flustered, yelling out in confusion. Beside him, Roanna was so shocked she froze, eyes wide open. In fact, even Hiroaki—the one who originally suggested it—was rendered speechless.

“We can’t change the facts. Sir Hiroaki wishes for Princess Rosalie to be his first wife.”

“That doesn’t mean you should agree to it so readily...! Wouldn’t Sir Hiroaki’s ties to the Restoration weaken like that?”

Are you in your right mind? Duke Huguenot implied without those exact words.

“Being married to someone you do not love would be agony for the rest of your life,” Christina answered smoothly, her tone as calm as ever. The “someone you do not love” here referred to Flora.

“B-But when you’re a royal or noble...”

“Indeed, such matters are irrelevant when you’re a royal or noble. However, Sir Hiroaki is neither royal nor noble. He’s a hero.” Christina continued Duke Huguenot’s unfinished words and smoothly dismissed them.

“That’s...” Duke Huguenot fell speechless, face twitching. If the subject at hand had been a young noblewoman, he would have dismissed such demands with a laugh, but he couldn’t do that with the hero.

“I have no objections to marrying a complete stranger if they bring benefit to the kingdom. If I don’t love them before we marry, I will strive to do so. But that is because I’m royalty—I cannot expect the same from Sir Hiroaki.”

“H-However, even then... The hero is absolutely essential to the Restoration. The best way to strengthen the ties of our organization would be...” Despite his difference in status to Christina and lack of consideration towards Hiroaki’s position, Duke Huguenot continued trying to persuade her with a strained expression.

“Of course, I understand how you feel. But the heroes are not originally from this world. They merely descended here by chance through the sacred summoning stones. They were originally legends passed down through the generations. Am I wrong?”

“That is correct, but...” Duke Huguenot looked dubious, unable to see the entire picture from just that.

“The heroes originally didn’t exist. It would be wrong to force them into the framework of our organization. Do you agree?”

“Since they exist now, I don’t think it’d be wrong to consider them in our calculations...” Duke Huguenot wasn’t about to back down easily. He didn’t often press his objections towards his direct superiors like Christina, but the hero held enough value to warrant it.

“Since they exist now, we have to consider things properly. But that doesn’t mean we can force them. The heroes transcend us humans, so forcing them into our society will create a distortion.”

Exactly like how we’re being troubled by this current mess, no? Christina implied with a smile that lacked any warmth.

Duke Huguenot fell silent at that.

“I didn’t exactly volunteer to become a hero either. If I could return to Earth, I would,” Hiroaki mumbled quietly.

A curtain of silence had fallen over the room, so his voice resounded well.

“In that case, would you like to quit being a hero?”

Christina wanted to ask what he intended to do about his engagement to Rosalie if he was saying he wanted to go back to Earth, but she decided to ignore it and get to the core of the matter instead.

“It’s not something I can quit even if I wanted to,” Hiroaki said sullenly. Christina was so composed that he couldn’t allow himself to get heated.

“The Restoration receives great benefit just by having you as a member of the organization, but if being here is a burden to you, then there should be room for further consideration.”

“So you’re saying you don’t need me in the Restoration?”

“Honestly speaking, the Restoration would be in a very bad place without you, so we would be greatly appreciative if you continued to remain with us. However, I wish to respect your opinion above all else. That is what I’m saying. These are my sincere feelings towards you, the hero, as the representative of the organization that wishes to keep you on board hereafter,” Christina said, making an appeal to Hiroaki in a truly dignified manner.

Hiroaki opened his mouth to say something, but no words came out. He fell silent with a bitter look.

Chapter 4: Return and Reunion

Rio and the others in the carriage arrived at the consulate from the airship harbor in less than ten minutes. Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan did most of the speaking on the way, so apart from the times he was specifically addressed, Rio was able to listen to Aishia’s telepathic communications.

In summary, Aishia and Celia had been living peacefully until they encountered Reiss inside the consulate one day. They chased him as he tried to flee and defeated him in a battle at the outskirts of Rodania. Though it took some time to hear the entire story due to the other conversation taking place within the carriage, Rio was caught up on the situation by the time they alighted from the carriage and entered the fortress.

So you’re saying Reiss is dead? Rio confirmed as he entered the front door.

Probably. But I couldn’t find his body. He disappeared without a trace after he was defeated. His presence was completely gone as well, Aishia answered a little uncertainly.

He summoned a lot of monsters before finally transforming into a monster himself, huh? And it was a monster you’ve never seen before, that disappeared the moment you defeated it.

Rio almost hummed out loud in spite of himself. It was hard to believe such a story. However, he had sensed a kind of creepiness from Reiss before, and it was hard to imagine Aishia lying to him.

Considering what you’ve just told me, it’s hard to believe Reiss is human. Since he transformed into a monster, it’d make sense if he really was a monster. But you said he didn’t drop an enchanted gem when you defeated him, right?

Rio confirmed the facts under the assumption everything Aishia said was true. If he had transformed into what looked like a vicious monster, then it was possible that Reiss was really a monster.

Monsters were creatures that left behind enchanted gems when they died, so if he was a monster, he would have left a gem. However, that wasn’t the case here.

There was nothing left behind.

Which means he isn’t a monster either, huh? But if he isn’t a monster, then what other options are there...?

Rio thought for a long moment. He had a humanoid form, and the ability to change into the form of a monster. The only other option he could think of was...

Could he be... a humanoid spirit...? Rio reached that conclusion.

I’m not sure. Reiss’s aura was closer to a monster than a spirit. But his presence is normally so weak that he almost seems like a human when he’s not doing anything. It’s weak enough to go unnoticed until he’s right nearby, Aishia added with more uncertainty.

Spirits could sense other spirits. To be more precise, spirits could sense the spiritual auras of other living creatures. Spirits themselves had the most unique spiritual auras, so it was easiest for them to sense the presences of other spirits. This was something Dryas had taught Rio.

Which means he’s closer to a monster than a spirit after all, huh... But there was no enchanted gem.

In that case, just what was his true identity? Rio found that questionable, but he didn’t have enough information to come up with an answer right now.

The other thing I’m wondering is what Reiss was doing in the Rodania consulate. Did it have something to do with Princess Christina and Princess Flora’s abduction, or was it for a different purpose? Rio wondered. The two princesses had been attacked while they were on an airship, not while they were in Rodania.

I don’t know. But Reiss snuck into the consulate right as the office was short staffed during the commotion from the princesses being abducted from their airship.

That was when Aishia had noticed Reiss, in the middle of escorting Celia.

So it’d be natural to assume he wanted to take advantage of the commotion clearing out the consulate to do something. Did he say anything that might give us a hint?

Nope. He kept saying he hadn’t meant to run into us. I think that’s why he tried to flee straight away.

Reiss’s true goal had been Celia, but because Lucius had acted on his own at the last minute, that truth escaped Rio and Aishia.

That part matches with the report Duke Huguenot received, I see. I was worried when I heard that Professor Celia saw a man resembling Reiss but lost track of him, but it was right to confirm the details with you first.

Celia made the report. She didn’t tell him that we pursued him and fought, but she said she had to mention the fact she saw him, Aishia explained.

I see... I’m so glad you were there by her side. Thank you, Aishia, Rio said with sincerity.

It’s fine. It’s my job to protect Celia when you’re not around.

Thank you, truly... Rio said, then paused for a long moment. I was able to achieve my goal thanks to you. I got vengeance for my mother and father.

Everyone really wants to see you. I’m glad you’re back too. Aishia’s voice echoed gently.

Thanks... I keep thanking you, ha ha, Rio said awkwardly.

Will you be with us forever now?

Yeah. Reiss’s purpose in Rodania bothers me, so I’ll try and stay with you guys as much as possible.

In which case, the invitation to Rio’s mansion in the Galarc Castle was a timely offer.

I’d like to gather everyone and tell them something, so let’s bring Professor Celia to the stone house tonight, Rio suggested.

Got it. Shall I head over there first and let them know in advance?

Yeah. But after we meet up.

Thus, it was decided they’d take Celia and head to the stone house tonight.

“We’ve arrived,” Marquess Rodan said from down the hallway. The party stopped in front of a certain room.

Aishia, I’m ending our telepathic conversation here. We’ve arrived at our destination.

Got it.

There were two female knights standing before the room they had stopped at, and they saluted Christina and the others with great emotion.

“Please enter.”

One of the knights opened the door for them to enter.

The interior of the room was spacious and tidy. There were another two female knights chatting to each other on the sofa, but they shot to their feet at Christina and Flora’s entrance, saluting them in a hurry.

“We’re coming in,” Christina said, approaching one of the many beds in the room. It was the bed Vanessa was sleeping on.

“So she still hasn’t woken up...” Christina grieved with a small sigh.

Indeed, this was the ward where Vanessa was recovering. After receiving a fatal wound on the enchanted airship, she had miraculously escaped death, but she was yet to wake up. Christina and Flora had come straight here after hearing that.

“Vanessa...”

Flora approached the bed and fretfully looked down at Vanessa’s face. Vanessa was as pale as a sheet, looking as though she was literally lying on her deathbed.

“Vanessa was the only surviving witness to what went on in the airship, so she’s been receiving VIP treatment here,” Duke Huguenot explained.

Vanessa was a well-trusted knight of Christina and Flora’s, so he was probably trying to emphasize his part in treating her courteously.

“Yes. As you can see, we’ve also placed her under strict security. While we’d like to hope it isn’t the case, it’s possible that a spy within the organization may try to silence her. Vanessa is beloved by her subordinates, so they’ve come to use this room as their break room just to guard her around the clock.”

Marquess Rodan praised the female knights in admiration.

“I see. Then I must express my gratitude. Thank you.”

Christina sighed quietly at the roundabout way Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan sought praise, then thanked the female knights in the room.

“Thank you for all you’ve done,” Flora said too, looking at the knights. Meanwhile, Rio stared at Vanessa’s sleeping face from behind Christina and Flora.

They said she’s been unconscious ever since she was injured, but this is a coma, right? If so, the cause is probably damage to the brain...

He wasn’t certain as he hadn’t studied medicine in his past life, but wasn’t damage to the brain one of the more likely causes of prolonged comas? For example, she might have bled to the point her brain function was impaired by the time the wound closed, or she might have struck her head hard while injured.

With that thought, Rio opened his mouth. “I only have a vague amount of knowledge regarding medicine, but may I ask a few questions regarding Vanessa’s condition?”

The existence of healing magic in this world meant that any wound short of a lost body part was easy to close up. Because of this, the development of medical science in certain areas was exceedingly behind. The use of cura was so widespread that in some regions the study of the human body’s interior functions was heavily avoided.

Thus, even Amakawa Haruto who hadn’t studied any medical science in his past life had more knowledge in certain areas than the people of this world.

“Oh? Are you knowledgeable about medical science too, Haruto?”

“Truly accomplished in everything, I see. Splendid!”

Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan immediately tried to butter up Rio.

“No, I’m honestly not that knowledgeable, but... May I ask how Vanessa lost consciousness in the first place?”

Rio looked at Christina and Flora, who had been there at the scene.

“After she was stabbed in the abdomen with a knife, she was kicked in the face and sent flying across the room.”

Christina looked back on the moment with a bitter expression.

“I see... Then, could you tell me which areas she was injured in, no matter how minor?” Rio asked next. This time, he didn’t address Christina and Flora who had been teleported before they witnessed the aftermath, but Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan who would’ve received the medical report.

“Injured areas, you ask? According to Roanna, who performed the treatment, the only area she was bleeding from was her abdomen...”

“In other words, the only area that was treated with cura magic was her abdomen?”

“No, after she was brought to Rodania, we had several sorcerers treat her entire body just in case,” Duke Huguenot answered, tapping a hand against his chin as he dug through his memories.

“Her entire body...” Rio thought for a short moment, then asked his next question. “May I ask what kind of treatment was done? For example, if you administered medicine or performed any other medical actions.”

“The knights would be more knowledgeable about that, as they cooperated with the doctors in nursing her,” Duke Huguenot said, looking at the knights in the room. “Well?”

“I see... We basically followed the doctor’s instructions to allow her to sleep in peace. Wiping down her body, cleaning excretions, using a tube to make sure she ingests nutrients and avoids dehydration... The doctor also said it’d be good to have someone beside her talking while she was unconscious, so we’ve been chatting to each other while in this room.”

One of the knights folded the fingers on her hand as she listed off their duties in detail.

“We considered the possibility of a curse on the knife causing her to remain unconscious and tried curse purification spells. We also considered the possibility of wounds invisible to the eye and spent several days casting cura and using magic potions for recovery. There was also the possibility of poison being used, so we mixed antidote magic potions into her nutrients. We thought of drawing blood to remove the remaining poison, but that idea was postponed as she’d lost so much blood when she was wounded,” the other knight added.

“Thank you for the detailed explanation. Was that everything?” Rio confirmed carefully.

The female knights exchanged a look and nodded. “Yes...”

It seems they’ve been attentively applying healing magic and recovery magic potions to no avail, so that means brain damage is causing this after all, right? With the level of medicine in this world, they wouldn’t know much about the structure of the brain and how to scan it... Assuming the brain damage is causing her to remain unconscious, what is the reason for that?

Rio looked down at Vanessa and contemplated the reason for her continued coma.

Was it because she hit her head when she was kicked away? Or, since it sounds like she lost quite a lot of blood before her wound was closed, was her brain deprived of blood circulation and damaged? Magic isn’t capable of replenishing lost blood...

Perhaps she barely managed to survive thanks to her wound being neatly closed while losing an almost lethal amount of blood. Or perhaps her face being kicked in was the cause. Rio guessed it was either one of these possibilities.

The brain is the most complex part of the body... Internal injuries are especially difficult to treat, and some wounds can’t be treated at all. What if the damage to Vanessa’s brain is especially severe? Severe enough for several hours of regular treatment to be ineffective...

If that was the case, then...

If her brain was treated with powerful healing magic, wouldn’t she be able to wake up? That possibility seemed reasonable.

The attention of everyone in the room had gathered on Rio before he knew it.

“Have you realized something, Sir Haruto?” Flora asked Rio like she was praying.

“I have no concrete evidence, but first, it’s certain that she lost a lot of blood when she was stabbed in the abdomen. Does everyone here know what blood is?” Rio asked, looking around the room.

“It’s a body fluid necessary for maintaining biological activity... I’ve learned before that the contamination of blood is a cause for many diseases,” Christina answered.

That was what Rio had learned in the Royal Academy as well. The method of drawing blood for detoxification that the female knights had referred to earlier was because of the belief in this world that drawing contaminated blood served as a treatment for disease.

Fortunately, they didn’t draw any more blood from her... She doesn’t have enough to begin with, Rio thought in relief.

“The reason for Vanessa’s coma might be because her brain received invisible damage, either from her face being kicked or from losing a lot of blood,” he explained briefly.

“Brain... You mean the part of the body within the head?” Christina asked in confusion, unfamiliar with the subject.

“Yes. She may wake up if you heal the wound in her brain with magic.”

While it was mostly impossible to treat a comatose patient with heavy brain damage using modern Earth medicine, wasn’t there a chance in this world where magic and spirit arts existed? Rio made his proposal with that in mind.

“Is it possible? To wake her up...”

“It seemed like she was unable to recover with just cura and magic potions, but the time required for recovery changes depending on the skill level of the healing magic caster, the time spent casting magic, the area treated, and the restriction of the magic effect range. Healing internal injuries is already difficult enough, but the brain is particularly complex, so it’ll be even more difficult. I don’t have professional knowledge either, so I can’t say for sure that it’ll succeed, but there may be potential in focusing on treating the head area,” Rio said, explaining how healing magic worked.

For example, a light injury would take mere seconds to finish treating, but a broken bone or internal injuries would take over ten minutes for the average healer to treat. Though this varied greatly depending on skill...

“I can use healing magic. Please let me try.”

“I can use it too.”

Perhaps they had found hope in his words, as Christina and Flora eagerly offered themselves up for the healing role.

“Is there anything we can do, Haruto?” Duke Huguenot asked too.

“Please prepare a large amount of highly nutritional cold liquid foods that Vanessa can consume easily and immediately when she wakes up. It’ll depend on her appetite, but prepare some easily digestible solid foods too. Blood is created in the body by obtaining nutrition, and there’s a limit to how much she can gain from a tube. She may still be lacking blood when she wakes up, so it may be better to have her directly intake the nutrients as much as possible.”

“I see. I shall make arrangements.”

“Then let’s begin treatment as soon as the food is ready.”

Thus, it was decided on the spot that they would attempt to treat Vanessa.

“Lunch hour has just passed, so we can prepare it immediately!”

The female knights left the room in a hurry. Less than a few minutes later, they returned. Then, another few minutes passed, and one of the servants of the consulate entered the room, pushing a cart.

“Your meal has arrived.”

The cart was piled full of cold foods. It wasn’t a realistic amount someone could eat after waking from a coma—not even a bulky man could eat that much.

“That’s too much,” Christina said with a sigh.

“M-My apologies. We gave the orders in a hurry.” The female knights apologized.

“It’s fine. This should be more than enough, at least.”

“Yes, let’s begin. Princess Christina and Princess Flora, if you could make your way to the opposite side of the pillow to me,” Rio said, moving to the side of the bed furthest from the door. Christina and Flora stood on the opposite side as ordered.

“What you’ll be doing is extremely simple. I will support Vanessa’s body, and you two will take turns casting cura on her head.”

“We just have to cast healing magic on her head...?” Christina asked curiously.

“Yes. Like I said before, the inside of the human head is extremely complex. Treatment will be quite difficult, so I don’t know how much time it will take. It could be a bit of a long endeavor, so please conduct the healing in turns to split the burden.” Rio lifted Vanessa’s head in his right palm, sliding his left hand around her to prop her up as he explained.

“I understand. Then I shall use cura first.” Christina stepped forward first, reaching her hand out to Vanessa’s head. She looked a little nervous and took a deep breath.

“Don’t be nervous. I’ll help too.” Rio smiled to calm Christina.

Christina tilted her head for a brief second but soon made an understanding face and relaxed with a smile. “Okay... Please do.”

“Ready when you are,” Rio signaled.

“Cura.” Christina recited the spell and began casting healing magic on Vanessa’s head. A magic circle appeared at Christina’s hand, emitting a faint light.

Right. Now I’ll enhance Vanessa’s physical body...

Rio casually activated his spirit arts, using his left hand to strengthen Vanessa’s body and right hand to heal her brain.

Spirit arts brought about supernatural phenomena in the form of materializing the imagination of the caster. And that imagination heavily affected the results. By casting healing spirit arts with a clear image of the structure of the body and its affliction, one would be able to effectively treat complex internal injuries.

And yet, Vanessa still didn’t wake up immediately.

“Let’s continue with the treatment for a while,” Rio urged.

◇　◇　◇

Several minutes passed. Rio and Christina were concentrating, so the rest of the room fell into silence. Flora also prepared for Vanessa waking up by holding a plate and spoon in her hands, waiting with bated breath.

Among them, Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan were watching with expressions that said “Healing magic and magic potions have already been tried extensively to no effect. Will she really wake up like this?” and an acknowledgment of “Well, let’s just watch on.”

There’s still no sign of her waking up, but the damage to her brain should be beginning to heal. I should try switching to a spirit art that stimulates her consciousness.

Rio secretly changed the spirit art being cast in his right hand from a healing one to one that interfered with the minds of others.

He believed it wouldn’t be good to use a spirit art that suddenly stimulated the brain when the damage hadn’t been healed yet, so he had waited until now. But in the end, he still found it risky to suddenly and strongly interfere with the consciousness, so he kept his output rather low.

Using spirit arts to interfere with another person’s mind without burdening it required a sophisticated technique, so he would leave the healing to Christina alone from here onward.

Healing magic itself required a constant and large output of magic to remain activated, taking quite a high degree of concentration. Christina’s face started to sweat.

“Shall I switch with you soon, Christina?” Flora asked worriedly.

“No, I’m still fine.” Christina smiled gently to reassure Flora.

Meanwhile, Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan wore expressions tha said “Is this impossible after all?”

While focusing healing magic on the head, a body strengthening spirit art would be applied to enhance the weakened bodily functions from being bedridden, and another spirit art would be used to stimulate the awakening of the mind. In this way, they performed a high level treatment impossible for Strahl humans to recreate by using spirit arts in conjunction with magic. However, to the others around them, it merely looked like Christina was casting cura on Vanessa’s head, so Duke Huguenot and the Marquess’s doubts were understandable.

If this doesn’t work, I’ll have to ask Professor Celia for her assistance as well... Rio thought, when just then, Vanessa’s body trembled.

“Urk...” A groan escaped from her lips.

“Vanessa!”

“Commander?!”

Christina, Flora, and the female knights noticed and reacted strongly.

“My goodness...” Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan were wide-eyed in wonder.

“Please call out to Vanessa, everyone,” Rio directed.

“Wake up, Vanessa.”

“It’s Flora. Can you tell who I am, Vanessa?”

Christina and Flora complied immediately from beside her pillow. They repeated similar phrases over and over again, while the female knights watching on called out to her with a “Please wake up, Commander.”

After a few moments, Vanessa blearily opened her eyes.

“Prin...cess...?” she said.

“That’s right. Wake up now,” Christina yelled as she cast cura.

Time for the finish. I’ll strongly stimulate her mind to wake up while strengthening her body. Rio increased the output of both his spirit arts.

“Ah... Ugh... Wh-Where...?” Life returned to Vanessa’s hazy eyes as she uttered sensical words.

“The consulate in Rodania. Do you know who I am?” Christina asked immediately.

“Pri... Princess... You’re safe...” It seemed she had a clear memory of what had happened before she lost consciousness.

“Sir Amakawa saved us. But worry about yourself right now. You were critically wounded and have been unconscious up until now.”

“Ah...” Vanessa let out a breath of relief.

“I know you just woke up, but do you have any appetite?” Rio asked Vanessa, supporting her from behind. One normally wouldn’t be able to eat at all after being bedridden with weakened organs and no ability to swallow, but a rumbling sound suddenly echoed.

Her body is being enhanced by spirit arts. It seems her digestive organs have been rejuvenated enough, Rio thought in relief. He normally used physically enhancing spirit arts in order to reduce the damage his body took or exceed the limits of moving around in battle, but by using it when a body’s functions were weakened, he was able to restore the body to a pseudo-healthy state.

“It seems like you do,” Christina sighed in relief, looking at her sister. “Flora.”

“R-Right away. Vanessa, open your mouth.”

Flora nodded eagerly and brought a spoonful of thick soup to Vanessa’s mouth.

“Mmm...” Vanessa swallowed the soup vigorously. The next instant, her eyes that hadn’t been quite focused regained their life.

“Ah, mo...” Vanessa moved her mouth, trying to say something.

“Mo...?” Christina and Flora tilted their heads.

“M-More! Give me more, p-please!” Vanessa pleaded desperately; she must have been starving.

Everyone in the room blinked in surprise.

After a brief pause, Christina broke into a gentle smile. “Feed her, Flora.”

“R-Right!” Flora’s face brightened as she brought the next bite to Vanessa’s mouth.

“Omph!” Vanessa eagerly snapped at the spoon. It was strange for a master to nurse her bodyguard, but Venessa currently didn’t have the mind or body to think about that.

“W-Wow. I’ll prepare the next bite.” Flora withdrew the spoon in a fluster, moving to scoop up the next bite of soup from the plate. Rio continued to touch the back of Vanessa’s head throughout this, secretly activating his spirit arts.

“N-No, I can feed myself! Mmgh, mmgh...!” Vanessa grabbed the plate with considerable force and brought her mouth directly to the soup to gulp it all down at once.

“Is it okay for you to be eating so fast...?” Christina asked in shock, but Vanessa’s eyes were fixed on her meal right now.

“Yes... Could you pass me that plate as well?” she said with a tremendous appetite.

Wow. I thought the most she’d be able to eat would be liquid foods, but the effects of the physical body enhancement is sure doing its work. Even Rio, the person casting the physical body enhancement, was wide eyed.

“Bring the entire cart over here,” Christina ordered with a sigh.

The servants immediately pushed the cart over. After that, Rio and the others had to watch Vanessa’s display of aggressively stuffing her mouth with solid foods, devouring them so greedily she nearly choked, and washing them down with drinks.

There was no conversation. Vanessa simply continued feverishly placing food in her mouth. Seeing her in such a condition made everyone think that she’d be okay.

◇　◇　◇

Roughly half an hour later, Christina and Flora led Rio out of Vanessa’s ward.

Vanessa had finished ingesting her required meal and was now sleeping soundly like a log once again. Since sleeping immediately after eating placed a large burden on the body, she wore an armband with a physical body spell enchanted on it. The magic essence needed to continuously power the band was provided externally, keeping the interior of the body stimulated as she slept.

Seeing how satisfied Vanessa looked as she snoozed comfortably, Christina decided there was no point in remaining in the room and suggested they head somewhere else. Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan left separately as they had information to discuss with each other.

“Vanessa sure had an amazing appetite,” Flora uttered in wonder, thinking back to what had happened in the ward.

“It was astonishing. But I’m glad,” Christina agreed with a relieved smile, then turned to Rio. “Thank you so much, Sir Amakawa. We keep borrowing your help, but we’ll definitely repay this favor as well.”

“Not at all. I wasn’t the one who administered the healing.”

“But you activated some kind of spell, right?” Christina asked, looking at Rio’s side profile.

“Well, yes... But I cannot tell the others what I was doing, so please don’t thank me for it.” Rio nodded while declining her gratitude. He’d told Christina and Flora about spirit arts, but he had no intention of telling anyone else.

“Then allow me to do something personally to thank you.” Christina wouldn’t back down either. Even if she couldn’t thank him publicly, she wanted to reward him personally.

“Please let me reward you too,” Flora immediately requested as well.

“If there’s an opportunity in the future. We have somewhere to be right now, though.” Rio changed the subject with a bit of a frown.

“Yes... We’ve just arrived. It’s this room.” Christina stopped before a certain room inside the consulate fortress.

“Are you sure it’s okay for me to enter?” Rio hesitated.

“Yes. Walking around the fortress serves the purpose of spreading word that Flora and I are both alive. She may be in the middle of a lecture, but we should go inside and ask for her permission to observe.”

That’s right. Inside this room, Celia was in the middle of teaching the noble children of the Restoration.

News of Christina and Flora’s return had already spread throughout the noble class of Rodania, but actually showing their figures in public had a greater influence on morale. Since they didn’t have any immediate work to tend to, it was decided they’d walk around the fortress at Christina’s order—who also invited Rio along.

“We might as well go and observe Professor Celia’s class. Would you like to come along?” Christina had said. Celia was apparently teaching several consecutive classes today, but this would be her last one.

Aishia, we’re about to go in.

Rio sent a telepathic message to Aishia inside the room first.

Okay. Celia’s panicking, Aishia replied immediately. He had given them warning the moment the trip was decided to spare Celia from the shock, but she was apparently shaken by it.

While that was going on, Christina opened the door a tiny crack, then pushed it open while peering inside.

“Let’s go in.” Christina entered the room first, followed by Flora.

Rio went in after the two of them and the scenery of the room entered his view. The room was an oblong shape, crammed full of students from their early to mid-teens.

Celia knew through Aishia that Rio and the others were on their way, but that didn’t mean she could tell her students that Princess Christina and Princess Flora were coming. She acted as though she had no idea they were coming to observe as she stood at the teacher’s podium to conduct the lecture.

However, the door had opened, so the lecture stopped. The gazes of the students flew at once to the door at the front of the room at once. Since the people that appeared were Christina and Flora, the students immediately burst into chatter.

“E-Everyone! Be quiet!” Celia slammed her palms on the podium, trying to quiet her students. She then moved away from the podium and hurried over to Rio and the princesses.

“Princess Christina, Princess Flora. And Haruto...” Whether it was from seeing the two princesses safe or from seeing Rio’s face again, Celia’s eyes were a little watery with emotion.

“I apologize for creating such a fuss out of the blue,” Christina said apologetically.

“Not at all. I’m overjoyed to see the two of you safe. I’m sure the students are all delighted as well. But why are you here?” Celia asked, tilting her head.

“Part of the reason is we wanted to show the hopeful youths of the Restoration our safe selves... But Sir Amakawa is also with us, so we decided to come observe your lecture,” Christina explained with an impish giggle. Her expression was somehow very natural, and she looked pleased.

“Is that so... Of course I don’t mind, but please give me a moment to explain that to the students.”

Celia blinked in wonder, then turned to look at the students. “Everyone, the safely returned Princess Christina and Princess Flora say they wish to observe our class today,” she informed the room in a loud voice.

“Oooh!” The students cheered happily. They knew Christina and Flora had returned to Rodania alive, but their main duty was to study. They had to hold back their desire to welcome them back at the harbor and instead attend this lesson, so there was no way they wouldn’t rejoice from Christina and Flora coming to visit them in person. On top of that, hearing the princesses wanted to observe their class filled them with motivation.

“Quiet, quiet now! We need to show them our usual class atmosphere. There’s no need to be too enthusiastic, but don’t look too pathetic either, okay? Pull yourselves together without making a fuss. Understood?”

Celia clapped her hands, calling out to the students. She seemed to have stimulated their pride well with those words, as they all replied “Okay!” in unison and quieted down.

“As expected of your masterful touch,” Christina said, praising Celia.

“They’re all fired up to show you their best sides.” Celia looked around at the students with a wry smile.

“Being able to take your lecture again, with Christina and Sir Haruto... It’s truly like a dream,” Flora said, sounding happy from the bottom of her heart. Rio sitting alongside Flora and Christina in one of Celia’s lectures was unimaginable back when they were attending the Royal Academy of Beltrum. Rio always sat alone when he attended lectures.

For some reason... It feels like the two princesses are a little different from before.

Celia had a faintly odd feeling. That was probably because Christina and Flora were now aware of Rio’s identity, but Celia didn’t know that yet.

“I’m glad your dream was fulfilled, then. Now, we can’t keep the lecture suspended forever, so please continue.” Christina seemed to sense what Flora was feeling and smiled gently. She then urged Celia to resume the lesson.

“There are some free seats at the back, so you may sit down there.”

“Thank you very much. I’ll also look back on the past while observing your lesson, Professor.”

Christina headed for the back of the room with Rio and Flora. A hundred pairs of curious eyes followed their movements with great interest.

“Say. Who is that guy? Is that man a noble?”

“That’s Sir Amakawa, I think. The honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom. The key figure in rescuing Princess Christina and Princess Flora, or something.”

The male students noticed Rio. Christina and Flora were walking around with a man their age, so it was only natural for the attention to gather there.

“He isn’t that much older than us... He already had achievements from when Princess Christina joined up with the Restoration, right?”

“He attended the party held back then too.”

“I heard he’s on good terms with Galarc’s king and hero as well.”

Some of the male students whispered to each other, wondering just how much he had accomplished when he wasn’t that far off in age to them.

For example, at the party held when Christina joined up with the Restoration, Duke Huguenot and Marquess Rodan had tried to set Rio up with young noblewomen. Due to this, Rio, who wasn’t originally well known among young male nobles, became known to some of them, and his identity was confirmed.

“Now, let’s resume the lecture.” Celia looked at Rio, Christina, and Flora all sitting in a row at the back and smiled softly as she restarted the class.

Come to think of it, it’s been four years since Rio’s watched me teach... Yeah, I have to give it my all as well! Celia thought to herself.

The same thought went through Rio’s mind. I never thought I’d take one of the professor’s classes again.

He watched Celia’s teaching figure with a pleasant expression. Celia’s appearance hadn’t changed at all in the last four years, so it really was as though time had rewound itself.

I sat down as I was told to, but...

The only difference between back then and now was that he was sandwiched between people who hadn’t been there in the past. If he turned to his right, there was Christina, and if he turned to the left, there was Flora. Christina was seated properly and listening to Celia talk. Flora had a cheerful grin on her face, but when she noticed Rio’s gaze on her, she blushed shyly.

Right... I should focus.

Rio immediately pulled himself together and focused on the lecture.

◇　◇　◇

“And that concludes today’s lecture,” Celia declared half an hour later.

Normally, that would be the signal for the students to all stand at once and crowd around Celia with questions and comments—or otherwise leave the room—but today, the classroom was deathly quiet. Celia looked around and saw no one walking towards her with questions, so she timidly made her way towards Rio and the others at the back of the room.

“It was a wonderful lecture as always, Professor Celia. I feel like I’ve returned to my roots by hearing one of your lectures again,” Christina offered to Celia once she approached.

“I’m honored, but... That’s an exaggeration,” Celia said shyly.

“No, it was truly amazing. I’m also pleased to be able to attend a lecture together with Sir Amakawa and Flora like this.” Christina shook her head with a soft smile, looking at Rio and Flora.

“Thank you for allowing us to observe your lecture today, Professor Celia,” Flora said, joining the conversation with a spring in her voice.

“You’re welcome. I could tell you were enjoying yourself while you were listening, so I had lots of fun teaching as well.”

Celia had seen Flora grinning happily throughout the whole lesson from the teacher’s podium; it made her smile as she recalled that.

“Aha ha, it’s all thanks to you three visiting me. Oh, that’s right. There are a few students who would love to have an opportunity to meet you. May I call them over here?” Celia suddenly asked, sensing the students’ excitement and smiling wryly at them.

“Yes, of course.” Christina didn’t know who it would be, so she tilted her head curiously as she agreed.

“Saiki, Murakumo.” Celia called the surnames of two students.

“Oh, so those two were also in attendance.” Christina caught on the moment she heard the surnames. Saiki Rei and Murakumo Kouta—they were the two who had escaped from Beltrum Castle with her.

Come to think of it, Rei mentioned that he’s dating a noblewoman now. And Kouta said something about training in the Restoration before becoming an adventurer... Rio recalled the last time he met them before he’d left.

“Have the two of them been well?” Christina asked.

“Yes. They both have the talent to become excellent sorcerers. They normally take the lecture with the ladies from Baron Dandy and Baron Gilbert’s houses, but... Huh? Have they left already? Saiki? Murakumo?”

No one showed up after Celia called them, so she turned to the seats where they normally sat. The gazes of all the students gathered there too.

“R-Rei, this is bad. We’re being called on,” Kouta said.

“Sir Kouta is right. You must answer when you’re summoned—especially since Princess Christina and Princess Flora are here,” Rosa added.

Rei shook his head. “Uh, no. If we go out now, we’ll definitely stand out.”

Kouta, Rei, and Rosa Dandy, who was dating Rei, all sat in a row. It seemed like Rei didn’t want to stand out in class, so Kouta and Rosa were urging him to move with hushed voices. However, he kept his head down to hide himself.

“Reacting like this will make you stand out even more, you know? It’ll only get worse the more you put it off,” a girl named Mikaela Belmond pointed out in amusement. She sat on Rosa’s other side.

“Guh... I guess I don’t have a choice. Let’s go, Kouta. You come too, Rosa.” Rei seemed to find his resolve and urged his underclassman up, grabbing the hand of his fiancée as he stood up himself.

“Wait, Sir Rei!”

“Enjoy yourselves, you three.” Mikaela saw them off with a wave.

“Why must I go as well...” Rosa murmured nervously.

The two of them do seem to be doing well. They hadn’t changed at all since their journey together. Rio chuckled to himself.

“Aha ha...” Celia laughed awkwardly.

“You both look well,” Christina said once Kouta and Rei approached, smiling in exasperation. Flora wasn’t acquainted with either of them, so she backed away shyly.

“Yes, fortunately. We’re glad you’re safe as well,” Kouta said, nodding.

“I, err, offer my sincerest congratulations on your safe return, Princess Christina, Princess Flora...” Rei placed a hand over his chest and gave a respectful noble’s greeting. His fluency was still a little shaky, but his intent was clear.

“Thank you. It was all thanks to Sir Amakawa,” Christina said, looking at Rio.

“It’s good to see you again, Rei, Kouta. I’m glad to see you in good health,” Rio said.

“We heard you saved the princesses again. You’re so cool, Haruto,” Kouta said in awe.

Rei nodded along. “Yes, yes. Sir Amakawa is truly the man of the hour.”

“Have you changed the way you speak, Rei...?” His words sounded oddly noble-like.

“Oh, well, I have to worry about how people perceive me now. My fiancée is in the process of teaching me how to speak properly. You are a foreign noble, an honorary knight equivalent to someone who holds the title of count, so if I don’t act appropriately, I’ll be scolded for it later...” Rei answered honestly, looking at Rosa.

Don’t you dare say anything strange, Rosa said with her glare.

“H-Honestly, I’m really nervous. Nobles sure have it hard.” Rei noticed Rosa’s gaze and brushed it off with a slightly panicked laugh.

“Indeed,” Rio agreed with an amused look. “If you’re engaged now, does that mean you’ve become nobility?”

“Yes. I received the title of baronet from Princess Christina. This is my fiancée, Rosa Dandy,” Rei said, introducing the girl beside him to Rio.

“I-It’s a pleasure to meet you. My name is Rosa Dandy. It is my greatest honor to be able to greet Princess Christina, Princess Flora, and Sir Amakawa like this.”

Rosa seemed rather nervous, but she was able to give a better noble’s greeting than Rei could; a baron’s daughter would normally be too far down the ladder to ever speak with the two princesses. As an honorary knight, Rio’s status was also higher, equivalent to a count, and he was the man of the hour, like Rei had said, so her nerves were most understandable.

“I see. It’s nice to meet you. I’m Haruto Amakawa.” Rio returned the greeting politely.

“I’ve heard all about you from Sir Rei, so, umm, it’s an honor to be able to meet you.”

“I was also greatly indebted to Rei on our journey to Rodania, so the honor’s all mine.”

“Umm, I’m pretty sure I was relying on you the whole time...” Rei muttered while scratching his cheek.

“Rosa, was it? Baronet Saiki is a good friend of the hero, Rui, so make sure you support him,” Christina said to Rosa.

“Y-Yes, Your Highness! I will make sure to do so.” Rosa bowed her head solemnly.

“I’d love to talk to you two some more, but it’s hard to talk in peace here. Perhaps at a later date... Hmm. We’ll be heading to Galarc’s capital again in a week’s time. Would you like to come too?” Christina asked Kouta and Rei, having come up with the idea in the middle of speaking.

“To the Galarc capital, you say...?”

“Sure, I don’t mind...”

Kouta and Rei exchanged a look and nodded.

“All right. I’ll contact you again with more details soon,” Christina said.

“Okay,” the two replied in unison.

“Do you have time after this, Professor Celia? I’d like to speak to you, along with Sir Amakawa and Flora.”

“Of course. I don’t have any classes for the rest of today.”

“Then let’s change rooms. It doesn’t seem like the students will go home if we stay here,” Christina said, standing up. Thus, Rio and the others relocated to have their talk.

Chapter 7: Tea Party Turbulence?

Meanwhile, lively conversation was also taking place elsewhere in the Galarc Castle, at the tea party being hosted in Rio’s estate.

It was a gathering where multiple people had never met each other before, but even they were able to chat with each other happily, as Charlotte was able to bring them into the conversation naturally.

Before they knew it, an hour had passed and the awkward atmosphere had pretty much dissipated. They weren’t the best of friends with each other yet, but even people who only just met each other were able to interact without reservation.

The current topic was Rio’s cooking skills.

“Hmph, it’s so unfair everyone else here has tried it. I wish to try Sir Haruto’s cooking as well,” Charlotte said with a pout.

Sir Haruto, Sir Haruto. Please cook for me as well, Charlotte pleaded with her gaze.

“I’m not that great at it, but... if you’d like, I could make one dish for dinner tonight?” Rio suggested to Charlotte, scratching at his cheek.

“Really?!” Charlotte brightened dramatically.

“Sure. I’ll go now to check the pantry for ingredients that I can use. I’ll talk to the chef and see if they can handle the preparations too,” Rio said, standing up from the sofa.

“Do you need help, Haruto?” Orphia and Miharu immediately offered, being that they were the best cooks of the group.

“No, I was the one who accepted Princess Charlotte’s request. You should stay here and relax. I’ll return in an hour or so at the earliest.” Rio declined and left the room.

◇　◇　◇

The door shut behind Rio as he left, closing with a snap.

“I suppose now is the perfect time. While Sir Haruto is away, I’d like to ask everyone something,” Charlotte suddenly said, looking around.

“What is it?” Christina asked first.

At that, Charlotte’s eyes sparkled in delight. “What kind of a relationship does everyone want to have with Sir Haruto in the future?” she asked all the girls present.

Most of them were startled, and the room fell silent.

“I’ll answer! I want to be with Onii-chan forever!” Latifa replied, raising her hand first.

“As his little sister, you mean? I thought you weren’t related to Sir Haruto by blood...”

“As both his little sister, and... a woman...!” Latifa didn’t falter under Charlotte’s calculating gaze. She answered her boldly.

“I’m going to be with Haruto forever as well,” Aishia said.

“You mean that in the same way as Lady Suzune, as a woman, right...?” Charlotte asked to confirm, tilting her head at Aishia’s words. She probably couldn’t imagine someone purehearted like Aishia in an intimate relationship with Rio.

“I am a woman, you know?” Aishia also tilted her head curiously.

“Mm, that’s not what I’m saying. I’m asking if you want to be in a relationship with Sir Haruto as a man and woman. Like marrying and raising a family. Do you want to be with him in that way?” Charlotte asked her question again, this time saying more to explain her intentions.

“No matter the type of relationship, I will remain by Haruto’s side. As long as he wants me there.”

“I see...” Impressed by something, Charlotte’s eyes widened in wonder.

“What about everyone else?” she asked the others once again. But no one replied after Latifa and Aishia.

Miharu, Celia, Satsuki, Liselotte, Sara, Orphia, Alma, Christina, and Flora all fell silent.

“Hmm, I see. That means the only ones with clear affection for Sir Haruto are Lady Suzune, Aishia, and myself.” Charlotte looked around at everyone in confirmation, before casually revealing her own feelings for Haruto.

“Come on Char, you can’t put people on the spot like that. No one understands why you’re asking such a thing,” Satsuki protested with a sidelong glance at Miharu.

“Oh my, you’re right. It seems I was overeager. There are some people here who’ve known for a while now, but as I just said, I am in love with Sir Haruto as a member of the opposite sex and would like to marry him if possible. Thus, I wish to know how the women around Sir Haruto feel about him,” Charlotte said in a clear voice.

She definitely omitted the explanation on purpose.

Satsuki narrowed her eyes at Charlotte. She had probably tried to surprise them in order to sound out their reactions. Satsuki was able to understand her fairly well now.

“I’m extremely pleased to have obtained the information that Lady Suzune and Lady Aishia are clear rivals. Though I don’t know how everyone else feels...”

Charlotte grinned as she looked around at the faces of those who didn’t answer, further assessing their reactions. Christina, Orphia, Alma, and Liselotte maintained their poker faces, but the others looked like they had some feelings for Rio. Her senses were sharp enough to spot that much.

I don’t know about Princess Christina, Lady Orphia, Lady Alma, and Liselotte, but there’s no doubt the others feel affection for Sir Haruto.

Charlotte giggled in a show of joy. “I’m sure Sir Haruto will receive lots of marriage proposals from now on, so I highly recommend those of you hiding your feelings to become more honest with yourselves soon,” she said to fluster those who hadn’t answered. They remained silent, but they each had slightly more panicked looks on their faces. Charlotte observed all their reactions and beamed in delight.

Well, I don’t doubt father will repel most of those proposals, though. But since she had said that to incite their sense of panic on purpose, she wasn’t about to reassure them with that information.

“Is this a declaration of war, Princess Charlotte?” Latifa asked, eyes burning with a sense of rivalry.

“You don’t need to call me by my title. I’m one year older than you, so I don’t mind if you call me Char, as if I were your big sister. I may really become your older sister for real one day.” Charlotte seemed to be truly enjoying the situation, grinning so widely she had to control her facial muscles from loosening.

“Hmph. Please answer me, Princess Charlotte.” Latifa urged her to answer, puffing up her cheeks.

“If Sir Haruto only chooses one person, then it’d be a declaration of war, I suppose. However, since that isn’t the only possibility, I’d like to form a cooperative relationship with you, with consideration for the future.”

“What other possibility...?”

“Polygamy. In other words, Sir Haruto marrying multiple women. But in that case, there’ll be limited positions available for the wives, so there may be competition there instead.”

Despite saying she wanted to form a cooperative relationship, Charlotte made sure to add an extra comment to stimulate a sense of panic, as she seemed to find things more fun that way.

“Hmm... I don’t think Haruto’s the type who can accept polygamy,” Satsuki muttered.

“Why do you think that?”

“He’s too awkward to do that kind of thing, don’t you think? I reckon once he falls for someone, he’ll love only that person until the end.”

“I think so too. That part of him is wonderful, isn’t it?” Charlotte sighed dreamily.

Latifa nodded in agreement. Meanwhile, Celia, Sara, and Flora also gave small nods at Satsuki’s words.

“Umm, if you think so too, then there’s no point in continuing under the assumption he’ll marry multiple wives, is there?” Satsuki said tiredly.

“No, no, there’s still the chance he’ll come to accept the idea of marrying multiple wives.” Charlotte was extremely optimistic.

“Well, it’s not like I know what Haruto’s thinking. I’m just guessing.” Satsuki sighed as though to expel her worries.

“Sir Amakawa did say that he was opposed to the idea of multiple wives,” Christina offered.

“Oh my, is that so? I would love to hear more about that,” Charlotte said, immediately latching onto that information.

“Anything further would involve Sir Amakawa’s own intentions, so I’m afraid I can’t say anything more than my surface impression.”

“I’m very, very curious, but I suppose there’s no helping it.” Charlotte pouted but accepted Christina’s troubled refusal with reluctance.

“Realistically speaking,” Charlotte said, moving on to a new topic, “if he were to only choose one wife in a monogamous relationship, I don’t have much confidence in being picked. Is that the same for everyone else? Unless there’s someone here who already has that kind of relationship with Sir Haruto...”

“Hmph...” Not even Latifa could reply boldly right away.

The others were also silent.

“It seems like no such person exists yet, so I’m very relieved. That means I still have a chance, after all,” Charlotte said brightly. “However, the problem lies in whether Sir Haruto actually sees us as members of the opposite sex. In my opinion, Sir Haruto is a rather late bloomer in that sense, and at the same time very gentlemanlike, so he never shows any sign of ulterior motives,” she added with a gloomy look. There was no way for her to know if she was being seen as a woman like this.

“You understand him well, Princess Charlotte...” Latifa was impressed, shooting Charlotte a look of acknowledgment. She realized she couldn’t underestimate her as a rival in love—with the potential that she was a dark horse.

“Thank you very much. I wasn’t born and raised as royalty for nothing. It pleases me to hear that from his adopted sister.” Charlotte thanked her with a charming grin.

“Even when he’s around the people he’s close to, he doesn’t do anything to close the distance himself. But that seems to have changed a little since he returned from his journey... Until now, we’ve always had to be the one proactively approaching him if we wanted to close the distance. Even then, I don’t know if he sees us as members of the opposite sex.” Latifa seemed to have her own thoughts about that, as her expression was rather conflicted.

“Is that so... In that case, it seems we should set aside the polygamy talk for now and first confirm whether Sir Haruto actually sees us in that way.” Charlotte started devising a plan to capture Rio.

“It’s not as simple as that, though...” Sara joined in the conversation with a look of determination.

“He’s afraid of losing his connections to people. It’s not that he hates connecting with people. I believe there’s a latent part of him that fears getting too deeply involved with others.” Celia also gave her analysis of Rio in a natural manner. She followed up on Sara’s response, but it wasn’t as though she had felt forced to do so.

“This has been extremely enlightening.” Charlotte looked delighted at the flow of conversation.

“If you want to get close to Onii-chan, you have to proactively press him. You can’t hold back at all, not even in the slightest.”

Latifa pointed out the most vital point in getting close to Rio. Although she wasn’t active in the conversation, Flora was also listening with a serious look of contemplation. Beside her, Christina and Liselotte were also listening in interest.

Everyone likes Haruto... I know she said as much the last time we left the castle, but Princess Charlotte is serious about Haruto as well... Miharu was also an introvert, so she had remained silent until now, but she had many thoughts going on inside of her. Like the others present, the atmosphere in the room was beginning to agitate her.

After the banquet, her feelings for Rio had been unintentionally revealed when Takahisa nearly kidnapped her. But nothing had changed in their relationship since then. She was fine when they were together in a large group, but when she was alone with Rio, she’d remember how he was aware of her feelings and become too embarrassed to function. Besides, they had spent most of their time apart after the banquet.

I can’t just stay like this, can I? Miharu thought with renewed enthusiasm. Rio had said they’d have more time together from now on, but she was faintly aware that their relationship wouldn’t change at the current rate.

Yeah. I can’t run away just because I’m embarrassed. Because I’m in love with Haruto as well... Miharu strongly recognized the need for change. Because she loved him—she was in love with him. Not only with the Amakawa Haruto from Earth, but with the Rio of this world too. That’s why she had no intention of giving him up to someone else. She didn’t want to. Charlotte had stimulated her sense of danger and made her recall how she’d felt during the banquet.

“I have one suggestion I’d like to make,” Charlotte said, as though she had been waiting for the right moment. Everyone’s attention gathered on her.

“In order to confirm whether Sir Haruto sees us as eligible women, how about we use today to plant a trap?” Charlotte proposed.

“Are you assuming that everyone here’s in love with Haruto?” Satsuki interrupted with an unimpressed look.

Everyone who’s lived with Haruto aside, Princess Christina and Princess Flora are here as well, you know? Satsuki looked at the two of them as though to say just that.

“No, of course I’m not assuming that. That’s why participation will be purely optional. If you like Sir Haruto, feel free to join in. Of course, if you have other motives... For example, if you want to join because you find it interesting, I won’t mind either,” Charlotte replied clearly.

“I see... But what kind of trap are you planning?” Satsuki asked.

“Let’s see. The most direct approach would be to bring up the topic of love in front of Sir Haruto, I suppose. For example, we could ask him which one of us is his type... That may be interesting to witness.”

“Do you think Haruto would answer that?”

“Indeed, Sir Haruto would probably be on guard if I asked such a thing in front of everyone else. In which case, it may be more realistic to have the people here form small groups and visit Sir Haruto to talk to him. That being said, it’d be extremely unnatural if we visited him in succession to talk about love, so we should come up with different topics once we’ve split into groups. Also...” Charlotte placed her hand over her mouth in thought. “It may be better to have those who don’t need to know if Sir Haruto sees them as attractive to participate, actually. It’d be better camouflage. Let’s treat this as an event in order to deepen our relationship with Sir Haruto. There are things we’ll only be able to say because of the atmosphere here right now,” she said in summary.

“I think that’s a great idea!” Latifa immediately agreed.

“Thank you. Anyone else? If anyone would like to sit out, please raise your hand.”

No one raised their hand.

“Then let’s decide our groups and what we’ll talk about before heading to Sir Haruto.”

And so, an event to deepen their relationships with Rio was secretly hosted without the man himself present.

◇　◇　◇

Half an hour or so later, Rio was preparing dinner in the kitchen. It was quite rare to see a noble cook, so the servants of the mansion that were off duty were watching him curiously. Among them were Liselotte’s attendants, including Aria and Vanessa.

Rio looked a little uncomfortable with being at the center of so much attention, but his skills were still exquisite enough to impress his spectators.

Incidentally, the dish he was making was a rice-style croquette using barley as the main ingredient. He made an elaborate sauce and added risotto-style seasoning to the barley.

Okay, that’s the preparation done.

All that was left was to fry it in oil before they ate. He had prepared plenty of ingredients so that there would be enough for a large number of people. The ingredients that couldn’t be exposed to open air had been placed in a bowl and covered in wrapping paper, then moved into a refrigerator powered by sorcery.

“Haruto.”

Satsuki’s voice echoed in the kitchen, and Rio turned around at the sound of his name being called.

“Hey, Satsuki—and Orphia, Princess Christina, and Princess Flora...”

Rio was somewhat surprised by the four people standing at the kitchen entrance. He called their names as the spectating servants made a quick and clean exit.

“Hey! Did we surprise you?” Satsuki said with a slightly awkward expression.

“Not surprised, but it’s just strange seeing the four of you together. Did something happen?”

“Nah, it’s just that we rarely get a chance like this, so we were talking about taking some time to group up in unusual combinations.”

“I see. I think that’s a great idea.”

“Are you still in the middle of food prep? Would you like to talk to us for a bit?”

“I just finished up here and was about to return to everyone anyway. Sure,” Rio agreed readily.

“Then let’s go to the dining room over there.”

“All right.”

And so Rio and the girls moved from the kitchen to the connected dining room. The five of them sat down at one corner of the enormous dining table that could seat thirty people.

“Sorry for making you cook by yourself, but the food you make is truly delicious, so I’m really looking forward to it!” Satsuki said to Rio.

“It’s no problem. Princess Charlotte was the one who requested it, and I like to cook. It was strange for me to be the only man in that room anyway,” Rio replied with a faintly strained smile.

“I don’t think that’s true. Right?” Satsuki asked Christina, Flora, and Orphia.

“While you were gone, everyone was talking about how they wanted to talk to you more. That’s why we came here,” Orphia replied first.

“Indeed. Everyone adores you,” Christina said, smiling.

“Yes. I also wanted to talk to you more...” Flora said shyly.

“If that’s true, then I’m honored.” Rio looked embarrassed.

“That aside, what were you making just now?” Christina asked.

“Croquettes with barley risotto inside.”

“Whoa, that sounds really amazing...”

“I hope you enjoy it.”

“We will! But wow, whoever ends up married to you will be one lucky girl.” Satsuki, who had been nodding with a smile, suddenly said this while examining Rio’s expression.

“What’s up? Why so suddenly?”

“Well, it’s just that you’re so good at cooking. It’s wonderful having a man who knows how to cook, you know?”

“Thank you...” Rio said shyly.

“While we’re on the topic, do you like girls who know how to cook?”

“Mm... I wouldn’t decide whether I liked someone or not based on their cooking ability.”

“Hmm. So they don’t have to know how to cook?”

“Yeah.”

“But you’d be happy if a girl made you food, right? You might grow more interested in them if they did. Wouldn’t you want to eat the food of the person you like?” Satsuki fired question after question at Rio.

“Well, I suppose that might be true,” Rio answered seriously.

“Would you be happy even if their cooking wasn’t the best?” Christina asked, joining in.

“Let me think. If it’s royalty and nobility, they normally never cook for themselves, so I’d be happy that they even thought to cook for me. I believe I’ve said something similar before, actually.”

“I see...” Christina hummed in great interest. Flora was also nodding in contemplation.

“Do you have an ideal type of woman you’d like to marry, Haruto?” Orphia asked next.

“An ideal type...”

“For example, a certain facial shape, hair color, hair length, or personality.”

“That’s a tough question. Can I say whoever I fall in love with becomes my ideal?” Rio answered with a frown.

Satsuki pointed a finger in warning. “No. You have to be more specific.”

“E-Erm...”

“Just one thing is enough, so pick something. It’s extremely important.”

“Uhh... Someone who doesn’t feel awkward to be around in silence, I guess?” Rio answered, wracking his brain.

“Hmm. So you prefer a quiet girl?”

“No. I’m not a very talkative person, so it might be nice to be with someone who can talk to me. But there’s no need for them to force themselves to keep speaking, and it’d be nice if the quieter times with them are relaxing...”

“I see, I see...” Satsuki nodded in deep understanding. The group then continued to throw various questions at Rio.

There’s an oddly large number of questions about marriage, love, and types...

Rio answered all of them sincerely, but he started getting a strange feeling partway through. Then, as though she had picked up on that, Satsuki spoke up.

“We had a girls’ talk while you were gone. Love and marriage is the typical topic in a situation like that, you know? We talked about various things, but no one had any experience dating, so we don’t really know how men work. You’re the man closest to us, so we wanted to ask for your opinion on a few things,” Satsuki said as though she was reciting from memory.

“I see... It sounds like you guys had fun chatting,” Rio said in earnest.

“We did. We’re normal girls for our age, so it’s normal for us to discuss things like that. Isn’t that right, Orphia?”

“Yes. We do it often when Haruto isn’t around,” Orphia said, giggling.

“It may be difficult to call royalty like Flora and myself ‘normal,’ but we enjoyed the talks very much,” Christina said.

“Yes. We heard many new topics and chatted like normal girls, so it was very fun. Thank you for inviting us to this party, Sir Haruto,” Flora added.

“Of course. I think you’re both very lovely, normal girls,” Rio said to the two of them with a gentle smile.

“Thank you very much...”

Christina thanked him somewhat bashfully. Flora was blushing to the tips of her ears.

He really says such things so casually...

Satsuki glared at Rio, looking like she wanted to say something. With his good looks, gentlemanlike demeanor, and talent, there was nothing left to be desired. Indeed, he would be popular like this; in reality, it was clear he was. His only flaw was how he would make flirtatious comments when he was such a blockhead himself.

“He really knows how to give people the wrong idea sometimes,” Satsuki muttered with a pout.

“Err... Satsuki?” Rio tilted his head at Satsuki’s gaze.

“Nothing!” Satsuki replied in a playful tone. “Now, it’s about time we went on our way. There’s a line after us, after all,” she said, then stood up.

Orphia, Christina, and Flora followed her lead.

“Do you have something after this?” Rio asked. He stood up with them, but Satsuki stopped him.

“We’ve actually decided to come and talk to you in order. So you should stay right where you are. The next group will come here once we return.”

“I see... Then I’ll be waiting here.” Rio let out a huff of laughter and sat back down.

“See you later, Haruto.”

Satsuki and the others left with the information they’d gathered, ready to share it with the following groups. As an aside, a cooking event for Rio would be held the next day—but that was a story for another time.

◇　◇　◇

After ten or so minutes had passed...

“Onii-chan!”

The door to the dining hall opened, revealing Latifa’s face. Behind her was Liselotte, and they both entered the room through the door.

“So it’s Latifa and Liselotte next?” Rio said. This was indeed a rare combination as well.

“Yup! Because the three of us had no time alone the last time we stayed at Liselotte’s house. We’re the group that was on the bus before being reborn! There’s lots we need to talk about, right?” Latifa said, taking her usual seat right beside Rio. It was a topic they could only talk about because they were alone in the dining room.

“The three of us never spoke in our last life, though.”

None of them had been particularly close. They had merely been passengers of the same bus that weren’t even on speaking terms with each other.

“We were practically three strangers in our past life, yet we’re now close enough to have sleepovers with each other. Isn’t it incredible?” Liselotte giggled, taking a seat opposite to Rio and Latifa.

“We were reborn and grew up in different places, but we still managed to meet each other again. This is what you’d call a miracle!” Latifa said, eyes sparkling.

“Yeah, that’s right,” Rio said.

“It sure brings back memories... I only started taking the bus after I met you, you know?”

“Wait, really?” Rio’s eyes widened. He hadn’t known that.

“Eheh heh, it’s true! After I missed my stop and you sent me home, mom said I could start taking the bus. I was too embarrassed to talk to you before I died, but I really wanted to get closer to you,” Latifa said shyly.

“So if you hadn’t started taking the bus, you wouldn’t have died...?” Rio asked with a somewhat guilty look.

“If you start thinking it’s your fault, I’m going to be mad. If I hadn’t been reborn, I wouldn’t have gotten this close to you.”

“I suppose that’s right...”

“I admired you in my past life. The handsome man that saved me. That’s why I don’t regret taking that bus at all! I love this version of you very, very much too!” Latifa hugged Rio’s side, expressing her affection directly with a carefree smile.

“The young woman that watched Haruto so shyly on the bus can now convey her feelings in such a direct way. I think that’s lovely.” Liselotte watched Latifa with a charming smile.

“I don’t want to regret anything. I want Onii-chan to know exactly how much I love him.”

“I think I know well enough,” Rio said happily.

“Really?” Latifa gave Rio a searching look.

“Yeah.”

“Hmm... I love you as a sibling, but I also love you in the way Endo Suzune felt for Amakawa Haruto, you know?”

Until now, Latifa had constantly expressed how much she loved Rio. Even though she had been somewhat able to convey those feelings with her attitude, she deliberately avoided saying anything directly about loving him as the opposite sex. However, the earlier conversation with Charlotte seemed to have acted as a trigger. The words came flowing out naturally.

“I see... Okay.” Rio had frozen for a moment with wide eyes, but he then nodded with a gentle smile. It wasn’t a bother. He wasn’t upset by it. He felt happy to hear it, but—

“I’m sorry... I won’t be able to give you my reply right away.” He wasn’t in the right state of mind right now to be in love with someone. Rio told her his true feelings, without muddling his words.

“That’s fine for now...” Latifa hugged Rio harder in understanding.

“Umm... Am I disturbing you two, perhaps?” Liselotte asked with a frown.

“Not at all. I don’t think I’d be able to say it if I was alone with Onii-chan. I was only able to say it because you were here and we were talking about our past lives. I feel really embarrassed right now, eheh heh.” It seemed Latifa was truly feeling shy, as she had a rarely seen bright red face.

“I see...” Liselotte smiled gently.

“As your little sister, being able to introduce myself as Suzune Amakawa or Amakawa Suzune makes me really happy. So that’s enough for now. Hee hee! Aren’t you jealous, Liselotte?”

“Yup, I’m really envious.” Liselotte nodded, still with a gentle smile.

“If you married Onii-chan, you’d have the Amakawa last name as well.”

“H-Huh?”

“Ah, Liselotte’s face is red. Look, Onii-chan!”

“Th-That’s because you said something like that out of the blue... Even if I wasn’t thinking about it before, I pictured it in my mind,” Liselotte protested with a squeak.

“Amakawa Rikka. Liselotte Amakawa.”

“S-Stop!” Liselotte blushed even more when Latifa said her name with Rio’s last name.

“Come on, Latifa. Don’t tease Liselotte too much,” Rio scolded her tiredly.

“Okay!” Latifa nodded honestly, then murmured to herself, “I consider Liselotte a rival too, though...”

Liselotte picked up on what she muttered by the movement of her lips, but she maintained her silence as though she hadn’t heard her.

“Hmm. All that’s left is... That’s right!” Latifa clapped her hands together as though remembering something.

“Is something wrong?”

“The truth is, there’s something I haven’t told Liselotte yet... I was thinking of saying it when I saw you again, but...” Latifa looked up at Rio’s face.

“What is it?”

Seated across from Rio, Liselotte looked puzzled.

“Erm... About my ears and stuff...” Latifa whispered in Rio’s ear.

“Oh... You should be able to tell Liselotte. I’m sure she’ll keep it a secret. It’s up to you whether you want to tell her, though,” Rio said without any particular hesitation.

“If the two of you want me to keep it a secret, I won’t tell anyone else,” Liselotte swore with a sincere look.

“Yeah, okay. I hope you won’t be too surprised by this...”

Latifa decided to reveal the truth about her species, and Liselotte spent a long time petting Latifa’s ears and tail with sparkling eyes.

◇　◇　◇

“It’s our turn next. What do you think of this four-person combination?”

Once Latifa and Liselotte had left, the next people to visit Rio in the dining room were Charlotte, Sara, Alma, and Celia. Charlotte and Alma sat on either side of Rio, while Celia and Sara sat opposite them.

“It’s natural to see Sara and Alma with Celia, but adding Princess Charlotte to this group is rather nice,” Rio said, giving his honest opinion.

“I’m glad to hear that. In households where the wives are on good terms with each other, the wives make an effort to mix up their lineup to give their husband a fresh feeling every day. It’s also said to prevent dead bedrooms at night.” Charlotte had a bright and cheerful expression, as though to say they’d be able to give the same effect if they were married.

“I-Is that so?” Rio said anxiously, causing his voice to crack. At the same time, Celia and Sara were blushing hard. Alma was turned away as though she had no idea what they were talking about.

“Speaking of which, I noticed today that you refer to Lady Celia without a title, Sir Haruto.”

Charlotte looked at Rio with a pout. He had always addressed Celia with a title when she wasn’t around, so she hadn’t noticed this until today.

“Yes... She’s allowed me to do so in private settings,” Rio confirmed awkwardly.

“Are you okay with that, Lady Sara, Lady Alma?” Charlotte suddenly said.

“Well, we’ve previously discussed how embarrassing it is to suddenly be addressed without a title,” Sara said.

“Indeed,” Alma agreed.

“Hmph. I also wish for Sir Haruto to call me Char.” Charlotte was truly frank with her feelings; she skipped the titleless name and went straight to asking to be called a nickname.

“Aha ha...” Rio laughed weakly.

“Will you call me Char?” Charlotte leaned coquettishly against Rio and pleaded. Celia and Sara narrowed their eyes faintly.

“No, I’m afraid that’s a little...” Rio tried to reject her gently.

“A little what?” With the distance between them still closed, Charlotte maintained her grin and feigned innocence.

“A little problematic for our social statuses. Especially if you’re not asking me to use your name, but a nickname.”

“Then I shall order you as the second princess. Call me Char.”

“Um...?”

“Go on, hurry up. If you don’t call me Char, I’ll give you an even more radical request.”

That wasn’t really a request, but a plain order, Rio thought to himself.

“Char...”

He had a bad feeling about the more radical request, so he had no choice but to call her Char, as ordered.

“Yes...! Now, once more. Call me Char once more.” Charlotte was immersed in ecstasy, repeating her request for Rio in delight.

“Once more, you say?” Rio asked, conflicted.

“Yes please. If you don’t...”

“I-I understand... Char.”

“Once more.”

“...Char.”

Charlotte continued making her request with an enraptured expression mixed with pleasure and delight. Partway through, she placed her head on Rio’s shoulder and started acting like his lover.

“Mmmgh...!” Rio could feel the piercing gazes of Celia and Sara seated opposite him. However, Charlotte continued with her requests without a care.

“Again.”

“Ch-Char.”

“You’re still being shy.” At this point, Charlotte removed her head from Rio’s shoulder to cling to his arm tightly.

“Now, let’s practice losing that shyness. Pet my head and call me Char. Come on, move your hand here...” She took Rio’s free hand and moved to bring it towards her own head.

“P-Princess Charlotte?!” It was at this moment that Celia shot up from her seat.

“Oh, my. Whatever is the matter?” Charlotte tilted her head curiously.

“D-Don’t you think you’re clinging to Haruto a little too much?”

Although they weren’t standing on ceremony today, Celia had held her tongue due to the status difference between the second princess of a foreign country and a count’s daughter. But there was no end to the flirting she was being forced to witness, so she finally reached the limits of her patience.

“Th-That’s right! I stayed silent because you’re a princess, but you’re going too far!” Sara protested strongly.

“But I don’t want to let go yet...” Charlotte took Rio’s face by the hand and gently turned it towards her, bringing him in close to stare at him.

“That’s enough.” Alma, who was seated on the other side of Rio, tugged at his body. She seemed to have a faint pout at her lips as well.

“Hnn... Jeez.”

Charlotte was slightly pulled off balance. She then puffed up her cheeks in an adorable pout.

◇　◇　◇

“So, last is Miharu and Aishia...” Rio sighed in relief when he saw the last two people appear.

“Sorry, we’re the only ones who aren’t a new combination of girls...” Miharu said apologetically.

“That isn’t a problem at all. I’ve been out traveling for so long that the three of us haven’t been able to spend any time together. It’s actually quite calming. Truly...” The memory of his earlier exchange with Charlotte made Rio all the more sincere.

“Right... That’s good, then.” Miharu seemed a little nervous, as her expression was stiff.

“Erm, would you like to take a seat?” Rio gestured for the two to do just that.

“Okay...” Miharu awkwardly started making her way to the seat across from Rio—when Aishia grabbed her hand.

“Let’s sit in a row.”

“Wha... Ai-chan?”

“You keep letting others sit beside Haruto, even though you always want to be the one sitting there. But there’s no one else around right now, so you should sit next to him.”

“Have I ever said anything about wanting to sit next to him?!” Miharu objected, blushing.

“Go on, sit.” Aishia pushed Miharu into the seat to the right of Rio, then sat in the seat left of him herself.

Miharu kept her head down and looked away from Rio in silence. She was clearly feeling very nervous.

Rio felt somewhat bad for her.

“Haruto...” Aishia said.

“What?”

“Miharu’s nervous,” Aishia stated, making Miharu flinch.

“Yeah...” Rio nodded awkwardly.

“You should call her Mii-chan.”

“Huh?” Rio was taken aback.

“What are you saying, Ai-chan?!” Miharu looked over at Aishia in a fluster. As a result, Rio’s face came into her view, as he was right beside her. When she noticed Rio’s gaze was on her, she quickly averted her eyes in embarrassment.

There was no longer any way of hiding the fact Miharu had feelings for Rio. Even Rio, who was ignorant to people’s feelings being directed at him, had noticed how much she liked him. He had also heard the truth from her very mouth during the banquet.

Ever since that day, Miharu had been too embarrassed to be alone with Rio. He sensed that and had avoided being alone with her as well.

However, he had really just been running away, so Rio had decided that he should say the things he needed to say. That was why he wasn’t about to run from the present situation. It would be insincere of him to keep brushing off his position on all this. He had to tell her his thoughts properly, at least once. He wasn’t about to let this rare chance to speak to her alone slip from his hands.

“Mii-chan...”

“Huh?!” Miharu gasped, looking back up at Rio.

“I’m calling you that right now, but in the end, the person I am right now isn’t Amakawa Haruto. Because until today, I’ve lived as Rio...”

That’s why he had achieved his revenge on Lucius. He wasn’t about to turn into Amakawa Haruto just because he’d done that.

“I... The current ‘me’ is Rio. I’m Haruto Amakawa, but not Amakawa Haruto. He’s a different person. I was raised in this world as Rio, and I’m not about to discard what I’ve gained as Rio.”

Miharu stared at his face, waiting for him to continue speaking.

“I know I’m an argumentative and tiresome person. I can’t become Amakawa Haruto. Once I realized that, I started thinking it’d be better to abandon him. That’s why I tried pushing you away. But I still have his memories. I tried to push you away, but I couldn’t. I don’t know what that means, or if it’s okay to be like that, but...” Rio still looked a little anxious as he spoke.

“I may be able to become Rio... who possesses Amakawa Haruto’s memories. I’m Rio, but I don’t want to run away from the person I was before, in Japan, anymore... That’s why to me, you’re both Miharu and Mii-chan. I can’t interact with you by completely becoming Amakawa Haruto, but these are my true thoughts. This is what I wanted to tell you—you, who sees me as both Rio and Amakawa Haruto...”

“It’s both. I think I love both of them. Haruto, from before he was reborn, and Haruto now. I fell in love with the same person twice.”

Those were the words Miharu had said to Takahisa, and the words that had convinced Rio to live as someone who possessed Amakawa Haruto’s memories.

“Y-Yeah...” Tears flowed from Miharu’s eyes as she nodded along. She finally felt like Rio, who had always been looking far into the distance, was seeing her as his childhood friend again. She was so happy.

“Rio.” Aishia called Rio’s name gently.

“Aishia...?” Rio’s eyes snapped wide open. Is this the first time that Aishia’s called me by the name Rio? he wondered to himself.

“You’re Rio. But you’re also Amakawa Haruto. So have confidence. There may be many hardships waiting for you in the future. But you’re the one who gave me everything when I had nothing...” Aishia said softly, her hand held over her chest.

“Thanks, Aishia...” Rio smiled gently. He then turned to Miharu resolutely.

“As the one who possesses Amakawa Haruto’s memories, there’s one thing I have to say to you... as Amakawa Haruto right now. Because I wasn’t able to say these words in my last life.”

“Umm... What is it?” Miharu braced herself with bated breath.

“Long time no see, Mii-chan. It’s nice to finally see you again.”

Sorry for running away from you until now. With a radiant smile the normal Rio would never show, he said to Miharu the words of reunion that Amakawa Haruto couldn’t say at the entrance ceremony.

Interlude: In Centostella

In a certain room of the Centostella royal castle...

Sendo Aki was dreaming. It was a dream from her childhood—a dream from nine years ago, before Haruto and Aki’s parents divorced.

Back then, she really adored older kids, she thought to herself. The Amakawa house had two working parents at the time, so they weren’t able to pay much attention to their children. The ones who looked after Aki in their place were Haruto and Miharu, which was why it was only natural for her to adore them as older kids.

Haruto was always close with Miharu. To Aki, they made the perfect pair. They were so close that they sometimes went off into their own world, but Aki loved watching the two of them play together like that.

“Haruto, Miharu...”

Before she knew it, Aki was calling Haruto and Miharu’s names in her dream. It was strange. Normally, just the reminder of Haruto being her older brother was enough to fill her with conflicted thoughts, but she didn’t feel anything unpleasant right now. Aki had returned to her childhood self—back to the times when she only had pure, unconflicted feelings.

A young Haruto and Miharu were reflected in Aki’s eyes. Their surroundings were pitch black; only the space where they stood with Aki was white. Beside them were the toys they’d used while playing house together when they were young. Whenever the three of them played house, Haruto and Miharu had been the parents, while Aki had always volunteered herself for the role of the daughter first. That way, she could be spoiled by her two favorite people.

Being spoiled by the two of them was Aki’s special right as their younger sister. And so there was only one thing Aki wanted to do in this situation:

“Haruto! Miharu! Let’s play house! I wanna be the child!”

Whenever she said that, Haruto and Miharu always agreed.

“Sure.”

“Let’s play, Aki.”

See? Haruto and Miharu were smiling as they nodded. With the three of them together, they could have fun playing house. If only such happy times could continue forever, Aki always thought.

“I want to have a sleepover with us just like this,” Aki mumbled softly in her dream.

Haruto and Miharu exchanged a look at that.

“It’s not a weekend day tomorrow, so we can’t,” Haruto explained with a troubled look.

“Aww... But I want to sleep between you and Miharu.” Aki’s head drooped in disappointment. She wanted to be with Haruto and Miharu more. She was envious of how close they were, but they never left Aki out and always included her with kindness.

“Mm... But the only days we can sleep over are on the weekends.”

“Isn’t there anything you can do about that, Haru-kun?” Miharu hesitantly pleaded to a contemplating Haruto.

“If you insist, then I’d like to...” Haruto hummed indecisively. “How about you sleep in my room today, Aki?” he suggested.

Aki’s face brightened immediately. “Huh? Can I really?”

“Sure. But Aki, you’re always sleeping with mom and dad, right? You won’t wake up crying, will you?”

“I-I won’t cry! I’ll be fine if I’m sleeping with you!”

“All right then. Let’s do that, Aki.”

Haruto smiled at Aki’s red-faced protests.

“Th-That’s not fair, Aki...” Miharu muttered quietly; she had been watching their conversation.

“Mii-chan. Don’t act like Aki now,” Haruto said with an exasperated expression.

“Hmph. I know...”

“You can sleep over at our place next weekend, Mii-chan.”

“Really?”

“Really.”

“Ehe heh.” Miharu beamed happily.

“Can I sleep together with you?” Aki asked nervously.

“Yup, sure you can,” Haruto and Miharu both replied while smiling.

“Ehe heh! It’s a promise!”

“Yeah, a promise.”

“Both of you have to stay with me forever, okay?” Aki pleaded with a broad smile.

“Yeah.”

“We’ll always be with you, Aki.”

Haruto and Miharu both nodded with beaming faces, when—

“Haruto? Miharu?”

Aki worriedly called out to them. Suddenly, Aki’s vision went completely black; she couldn’t see anything other than herself.

“Aki.”

In the darkness, she could hear Haruto and Miharu’s voices.

Oh, thank goodness... It’s my brother and Miharu... Aki rejoiced in relief. But that only lasted for a moment.

Aki woke up with a gasp. “A dream...” she mumbled to herself, sitting up in bed.

She really had awoken from a dream, because neither Haruto nor Miharu were in the Centostella Castle with her.

More importantly, the person who was once Amakawa Haruto was already dead. Yet he was also alive—he had been reborn into this world, and was currently living together with Miharu somewhere.

Why did I have a dream like this...

She played with Haruto, heard his voice, and felt happiness from it. It may have been just a dream, but why did it happen...? Aki wondered to herself with a bitter expression. A variety of emotions flashed across her mind in a single moment.

He didn’t keep his promise. He said the three of us would stay together. That he’d be with me forever. He promised, and yet...

Miharu didn’t break her promise. She stayed beside me even after mom got divorced. She spent every day with me, holding my hand while I was sad.

She was different from him.

But...

“Now Miharu is gone too...” Aki muttered tearfully, as though she was seeking some form of salvation.

Even Aki knew, deep down, that the feelings she had carried with her for so many years were unjustified. But logic was different from emotions, which was why she’d carried her resentment with her this entire time. She continued believing that she was the one in the right. She didn’t want to believe she was wrong.

But now...

“It’s morning...” Aki’s gaze wandered as though searching for someone, then landed on the window in disappointment. It was already bright outside.

Presently, as the siblings of the hero Takahisa, Aki and Masato were staying at the Centostella Castle as national guests. But there wasn’t anything in particular for them to do here.

Aki tried to visit Takahisa’s room every day, but they didn’t spend much time together. Ever since the incident in the Galarc Castle, Takahisa had taken to shutting himself away in his room.

He now preferred to be alone. While he was more relaxed around Aki, being that she was his step-sister, their conversations were awkward and couldn’t keep going like they used to, so he would tell Aki to return to her room and leave him in peace. Because of this, Aki rarely saw him outside of his room.

Instead, her time with her younger step-brother increased. Masato was busy continuing his sword training even after coming to Centostella, but he made as much time as possible for Aki, who was in low spirits these days. He always visited her outside of his training hours.

Back at the stone house... Or rather, back in Japan, Aki and Masato hadn’t been such close, clingy siblings. They were the siblings that commonly cracked sarcastic jokes at each other without any affectionate conversation between the two of them. But lately, Masato would spend long hours at a time beside Aki, even if it was just in silence.

Aki was so grateful for this that she naturally found herself visiting Masato whenever she wasn’t in Takahisa’s room. Their time together increased without her noticing.

“I wonder if Masato’s training this morning as well...” Aki mumbled to herself as she got changed to visit the training grounds.

◇　◇　◇

Ever since coming to Centostella, Aki and Masato had increasingly spent more time together, while Masato and Takahisa barely spent any time together.

After wandering into this other world, their family had finally reunited in this castle. Yet ever since the incident at the Galarc Castle, the three of them hadn’t spent a single second gathered together to enjoy each other’s company because of the deterioration of the sibling bond between Masato and Takahisa. When they first arrived in Centostella, Masato had still visited Takahisa, who stayed shut in his room regularly, but with Takahisa’s lingering guilt about the Galarc incident and Masato’s own thoughts on the events, a huge argument had broken out between them.

Masato had continued visiting Takahisa’s room despite arguments breaking out each time, but that seemed to be the wrong move to make. They were now in a cold war with each other and, as far as Aki knew, hadn’t seen each other in three weeks.

I have to be the one to help the two of them make up again... Aki thought to herself as she made her way to the training grounds with a gloomy face. Recently, her mind had been filled with negativity whether she was alone or not.

Aki had a female knight at her side as a guard, but they didn’t converse with one another. Thus, before she knew it, Aki had arrived at the training grounds.

“What is it, Masato?! Why’d you bring me out here so early in the morning?!” Takahisa called out.

“It’s your fault for not leaving your room in days! You know you’ll ruin your health if you keep living like that, right? And besides, Aki’s been down in the dumps these days. You’re her older brother yet you’re just hovering around doing nothing!”

Takahisa’s yelling voice echoed over. It seemed like Masato was also present, and the two were fighting. Aki ran over in a hurry, entering the training grounds.

“Lady Aki... Good morning.” Centostella’s first princess Lilianna noticed Aki’s presence and approached her.

“Good morning, Miss Lilianna. What’s going on here...?” Aki asked, looking over at Takahisa and Masato arguing a slight distance away from the entrance.

“I passed by Sir Masato on his way to the training grounds this morning, and the topic of Sir Takahisa came up...” Lilianna frowned with worry.

When he heard Takahisa hadn’t left his room in days, Masato had charged into his room in a fury.

“If you’re our brother, you should act like it.”

“What do you mean ‘act like it’? You’re just saying whatever you want.” Takahisa had a sour expression on his face.

“Haruto always thought of us first before anything. But you only care about yourself. Both back in Galarc, and ever since coming here, you’ve only cared about yourself. Why do you think Aki and I came to this kingdom with you?”

“The only thing that ever comes out of your mouth is Haruto this, Haruto that...” Takahisa’s expression turned grim at the mention of Haruto’s name. However, an argument of this level was still on the mild side of things—they had fought more fiercely before. That’s why they had avoided seeing each other until now.

Aki, unable to move, merely watched her brothers argue. She knew her words would have no effect on them. In fact, she wasn’t even sure if stopping them was the right thing to do. In reality, she had tried to stop their fights numerous times until now, but they were still at odds with each other. Merely stopping them was pointless—that was how she felt. However, she had no idea what she could do instead... Aki had absolutely no confidence left in her.

“Pick up your sword, bro,” Masato suddenly said.

“What?”

“I’m saying you should spar with me.”

“What kind of craziness are you spouting? There’s no point in doing that.”

“I’m telling you not to run away.”

“Run away? When have I ever run away? I’m not running away from anything!” Takahisa gradually grew more irritated.

“Then fight me. And if I win, you have to stop running away.”

“Like I said, I’m not—”

“You are, though. Shutting yourself in your room all day. You’re running from me, from Aki, and from Princess Lilianna. You’re running from everyone worried about you.”

“What...?” Takahisa wanted to argue back, but he couldn’t say anything back.

Before he could do so, Masato spoke up. “If you’re not running, then you can spar with me, right?”

Takahisa had no response.

“So you are running. How pathetic.” Masato snorted before shooting him a mocking smirk.

“Fine... I’ll fight you,” Takahisa agreed in a low voice. Either he had found his resolve or he thought he wouldn’t lose to Masato.

“That’s it then. Here.” Masato tossed one of the training swords at Takahisa.

“Hmph.” Takahisa picked up the sword from the ground in displeasure.

Lilianna exhaled lightly, then immediately gave the female knight beside her an order. “Kiara. You be the judge.”

“Understood.” Kiara nodded with respect, then walked towards the two of them. Thus, it was decided that they would hold a sparring match.

◇　◇　◇

Masato and Takahisa faced each other from different corners of the training grounds. Masato was equipped with a one-handed sword and shield while Takahisa gripped a hand-and-a-half sword in both his hands.

“I don’t wanna hear any excuses about how you were going easy on me after your defeat, bro,” Masato said. It was more of a confirmation than a provocation.

“We’re four years apart in age. There’s no way I’d lose to a child like you,” Takahisa replied sullenly, mood soured by those words.

“Hmph. I don’t know about that. I wasn’t the one who shut myself in my room. You don’t know how much stronger I’ve gotten, do you?” This time, Masato intentionally provoked him.

“Don’t look down on me.” Takahisa was even more sullen at that.

The acting judge, Kiara, stood between them, sighing quietly before mediating their argument. “Both sides, mind your mouths. You’re competing purely with sword ability. If I deem the match too dangerous, I will suspend it immediately.”

“I’m ready whenever, Miss Kiara,” Masato replied, holding his sword and shield ready.

Takahisa maintained his silence, but he also seemed ready to go. He held his sword while glaring at Masato with a stern look.

“Begin!” Kiara said, signaling the start of the match.

At the same time, Takahisa lifted his sword up and charged at Masato. He had no intention of sounding out Masato’s abilities or moves; he intended on deciding the match immediately. It was an action made on his firm confidence that he was the stronger one.

“I can see right through you!”

Masato aimed for the moment when Takahisa swung down and stepped forward. He charged with his shield first and deflected Takahisa’s sword when it was unable to fully swing down. Using his forward momentum, he lightly struck the pommel of his sword hidden behind his shield into Takahisa’s torso.

“Guh...”

There hadn’t been enough force to make it a painful blow, but Takahisa stumbled back under the force of the attack.

“If this was a match between knights, that would have been a telling blow. But we don’t have to count that one. It’d be too disappointing if it ended like this,” Masato said, giving Takahisa another chance.

The embarrassment he felt because he’d lost again against an opponent he thought was weaker just made Takahisa angrier.

“Go on, come at me.”

Masato hopped backwards, distancing himself without lowering his guard while spurring on Takahisa’s fighting spirit.

“Ngh!” Takahisa charged at Masato once again. The second round had started. Meanwhile—

Lilianna, who was watching the match beside Aki, turned to the captain of her knights. “What do you think, Hilda?”

“I could tell Sir Masato was more used to handling the sword from the moment he positioned himself. His movements are efficient, as though he’s experienced with real battles. I’m sure his own efforts played a huge part, but he has wonderful talent. Sir Amakawa’s instruction before he came to our kingdom must have been brilliant too.”

Hilda made no reference to Takahisa’s abilities and praised Masato highly. She often sparred with Masato herself, so she knew of his talents well.

On top of that, Masato persistently stuck to Rio’s teaching, doing his drills and sparring matches every day. Doing training drills every single day was something even full-time soldiers had difficulty accomplishing.

“It looks like Takahisa’s the one putting pressure on him, though...” Aki said, looking at their fight. Only ten or so seconds had passed since the second round started, but right now it looked as though Takahisa was overwhelming Masato with his stronger build as he swung his sword.

“Sir Masato is seeing through all of Sir Takahisa’s attacks and defending himself. If you wildly swing your sword while relying purely on strength, you’ll soon run out of energy. Sir Masato is waiting for that moment—a truly calm plan.”

That was another area where his real experience shone, as Hilda had pointed out. Indeed, Masato was deftly handling all of Takahisa’s attacks with his shield right now.

That ability comes from his experience rather than his intuition, I’d say. The ability to choose the best action for the situation was probably something Sir Amakawa drove into him. Sir Amakawa may be the type to fight logically.

While she didn’t say it out loud, Hilda added to her analysis in her head.

“I-I see...”

Aki looked a little conflicted as she accepted the explanation. Since she lived together with them, she knew that Rio had been the one to teach Masato. Those teachings had accumulated into this moment, which was causing her conflicted feelings.

Just then, Masato stopped his defense against Takahisa and made his move. He parried the trajectory of Takahisa’s swing with his shield.

“Let’s go, Takahisa!”

Masato proceeded to slip right up to Takahisa.

“I won’t let you!”

Takahisa reflexively twisted his body and aimed an acrobatic swing at Masato. The tip of his sword sliced the air, drawing a powerful arc. Masato instantly repositioned his shield to block Takahisa’s sword.

Normally, one would be surprised by the unexpected approach of the sword and freeze, delaying their reaction, so being able to read the attack clearly and respond without fear to block it was truly splendid.

Once he blocked the attack, Masato had no choice but to charge forward to eliminate any openings.

“Guh...” Takahisa had twisted his entire body to swing his sword, so he was awfully off balance as he landed on the ground.

My brother hasn’t practiced his basics at all and tries to use eccentric movements, which is what makes him scary. His reflexes are crazy, Masato thought tiredly.

“Hah!” Masato noticed the wide opening Takahisa had left and repositioned his shield to charge again. He proceeded to tackle Takahisa with the shield. Even though he was smaller than his brother, it was easy to topple Takahisa after he was staggering from his blocked sword attack.

“Ngh!”

Takahisa retreated on unsteady feet and slashed his sword horizontally with a pained look. But Masato stooped low and stepped forward sharply.

“Sloppy aim coming from you!”

The shield coming from down to up parried Takahisa’s sword. Masato then swung his sword in a compact move, intending on coming to a stop before making contact. This time, he secured his victory.

“I-It’s not over yet!” Just in that moment, Takahisa belatedly swung his sword. It moved much more quickly than Masato’s.

“Wha...?!” The unnaturally rapid speed of the swing slammed Masato’s sword out of his hands. Having been overpowered, Masato’s sword went flying, rotating several times as it danced through the air. Several beats later, it landed on the ground.

“Hey... Takahisa, you...”

Masato threw a fierce glare at Takahisa. In that last moment, it looked like Takahisa had used the physical strengthening effect of his Divine Arm. If he hadn’t done so, Masato would have won.

“I-I won,” Takahisa said in a slightly flustered high-pitched voice.

Masato paused for a long while. “I see,” he finally said.

“Please wait a minute. That last move—”

Kiara was bothered by how Takahisa had accelerated at that last moment, and she tried to speak up as the judge. However, Masato cut in and stopped her.

“It’s fine, Kiara.”

“But...”

“It’s my brother’s win, right? Yeah? And you’re really okay with that, Takahisa? That’s how an older brother should be, right?” Ignoring Kiara’s hesitation, Masato stared at Takahisa sharply.

Takahisa averted his eyes shamefully, falling silent.

“I see how it is... Then it’s my loss. For today. Let’s spar again sometime.” Masato turned around with a pitiful expression, then walked away from Takahisa.

Epilogue: Saint of Vengeance

Drastically different from Galarc was a tiny kingdom far out on the edge of the Strahl region. This place was worn down to its limits; it was cold and dry, and it barely got any rain at all. The land had all but withered away, and the citizens were famished.

The only ones prospering were the noble class and above. Only royalty and nobility were capable of an affluent life, and they made up less than one percent of the population. The majority of the kingdom was starving. That was how the kingdom existed until now.

The rich were no gods. Nothing could last forever.

The end came abruptly.

Change was trying to occur; the first change that would greatly shake the Strahl region was happening right at this very moment.

“Raaaaaargh!”

In the capital of the small, starving kingdom, angry voices roared.

Ten thousand people out of a population of a hundred thousand were marching forward. They had shabby weapons and armor—most were holding farming tools. Some weren’t holding anything.

Just minutes ago, those people had broken through the gates to the noble district and were now swarming towards the royal castle. Many of the buildings in the noble district were reduced to rubble along the way.

Leading the way to the castle was a black-haired woman in a holy dress, wielding a beautiful bishop’s staff like a mace. She looked to be around her mid to late twenties.

“Come, my devout believers. The time is now. Follow my lead!”

The woman raised her staff high in the air and called out to the people. Her voice was nearly wiped out by the angry cries, and it only reached the ten people immediately behind her.

“Today, as of this moment, I will pass the judgment of god onto this rotten kingdom. The rulers who hoarded wealth in the name of god will taste true divine punishment!”

She lifted her staff towards the castle, which stood on the cliff at the deepest end of the noble district, and raised her voice.

“Your anger is my anger! Your vengeance is my vengeance! Thus, I will bring down the hammer of justice on the rotten rulers of this world! Now, everyone! Release all your overflowing rage! Send it all to me!”

There was no stopping her—not her voice, nor her march forward. Their pace was only that of a half jog, but they were getting closer and closer to the castle.

“Send me your anger! And I... I... I shall erase it all! Erase it all, and build it up again! The people, and a society for the people! We must dispose of them! Of the corruption, those rotten rulers! We will create a revolution for the people with our hands! We will create a democracy!”

The only thing reflected in her eyes was the castle on the cliff. She recited her words as though they were borrowed from someone else, yelling them vacantly into the angry crowd. However, the wrath in her eyes was unmistakable. She undoubtedly felt a violent hatred towards something.

And so the woman advanced.

She closed in on the castle at the end of the noble district. However, once she approached within several hundred meters of the foot of the castle, she came to a sudden stop.

The people following her collectively halted as well.

“Vengeance is mine! I will reply!”

The woman looked up at the castle on the cliff while yelling.

“Vengeance is yours! Vengeance is yours!” the people chanted.

“Vengeance is mine! I will reply!” The woman yelled while raising her staff.

“Vengeance is yours! Vengeance is yours!”

The angry yells eventually filled the entirety of the capital.

“Vengeance is yours! Vengeance is yours!”

The woman felt the angry yells of the people against her back. Then, after an amount of time, she swung her staff down.

The moment the end of the staff hit the ground, the earth exploded, violently rising upwards. The explosive energy gathered towards the front, blowing the earth up and towards the cliffside where the castle was.

“Raaaaaagh!”

The people watched the spectacle while yelling passionately. The swelling earth rose like a wave, approaching the cliff.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, on the highest floor of the royal castle...

“Wh-What? What is this? What have I ever done to them?”

The king of the kingdom was trembling. The view that only those in power could witness up until yesterday no longer existed in the capital. Mere minutes ago, the gate to the noble district was blown away, the buildings in the noble district were destroyed, and the violent crowds were now drawing near.

“I-I’m scared. I’m scared... It’s terrifying, so terrifying...” The king shook violently.

I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared. I’m scared.

Only one emotion filled his heart, his head—everything. There were a thousand soldiers protecting the castle, but there was no telling if they were reliable enough to hold the fort.

A thousand could be killed in an instant.

Just then, the door to the room where the king was hiding flew open. The commander of the knights appeared.

“Y-Your Majesty! Please flee—”

The knight commander tried to yell, but his words were cut off before he could finish.

The last thing the king saw was the explosion that involved the commander and all the surrounding stone.

◇　◇　◇

Back at the foot of the cliffside...

“Aaaaaah!”

“As of this moment, this kingdom has obtained salvation! The rotten royals and nobles are gone!” the woman declared proudly.

“Whoooooo!”

The people cheered. They saw the divine sight of the woman—no, the saint—and cheered. The woman raised her staff once again.

“From now on, I will be your spear, your staff, your guide to the proper path. Now, let us build our own country on this land!”

While the saint’s voice was drowned out by the cheers of the people, her declaration to found a nation was not.